(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
A director is...
A title I've always dreamed of.
But to be a director...
Please don't get it wrong.
Why did you stop there?
- It's never easy. - It's giving me a headache.
A director is...
someone who decides the direction.
- Come forward diagonally. - Music.
Various textures.
According to the accent...
- Dance. - Three and four and...
Stage.
Someone who creates a work of art...
by integrating all those elements is a director.
There's so much to do.
- One, two, three, four, five... - I have to decide...
positions and movements.
I have to be good at teaching for people to understand.
- Really good. - Good job.
- I need to support the dancers... - That was wonderful.
And take care of them.
This is nothing compared to your effort.
It's a token of gratitude.
Take one step back, please.
See if they're moving smoothly.
Make sure they don't bump in and prevent any accidents or issues.
- I have to check everything. - Help Noura move forward.
You have to move faster.
They could get hurt.
Move the lights slower than that.
I should be able to control the timing for the lights.
- You can do it. - Come in here...
Can you make sure that I can use the area in the back?
I'm showing the performance that I directed.
There's so much for me to handle alone.
I have to bear the pressure and responsibility.
(Heavy responsibility on directors)
It might appear to be impressive and amazing.
But directors are actually very lonely.
(A lonely job where they spend most of the time alone)
It's a battle with myself.
From here.
(A battle with myself that only I know)
Still, the result...
- makes me happy. - That's incredible.
When my idea becomes real,
I'm like, "This really works."
(A sense of accomplishment when an idea becomes reality)
When my idea becomes reality.
When it receives a good response.
When people are touched by my work.
We do it because it makes us happy.
A show like this is perfect because they're given many opportunities...
to put on a performance where real responsibility is...
- on the line. - Two, three, four...
If they direct even one song in detail...
It gave me an opportunity to grow.
This is a very good opportunity.
I'm grateful because it's allowing me to try...
- We can do it. - what I want.
- The thing is... - I want to show what I'm like...
- as a director. - Okay.
I want to continue to create good pieces.
(I want to continue to create good pieces.)
Let's go!
Let's...
(Today)
(We're the dummies this time.)
(A dancer?)
(We're dancers.)
(Hey, we're becoming dancers.)
(There's only one director.)
(It's the director version of the Class Mission.)
(The second mission)
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(The directors are receiving directions.)
(Never ever.)
(I can never let that happen.)
(I don't want to be a dancer.)
(I'll have to become a director.)
(The Draft Creation Mission is given to 10 choreographers.)
(Who will become the ultimate director?)
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
NaiN versus BABYZOO.
You'll now begin casting dancers.
Hello. I'm BABYZOO.
My signature song is...
"WHERE YOU AT" by ALLDAY PROJECT.
Her signature song is...
You're so "RUDE!" by Hearts2Hearts.
(Did he just call NaiN rude?)
Toward her.
(She suddenly became rude.)
That's scary.
My number one priority was Lee Jung.
- She appeared in this show twice. - Oh, Lee Jung.
Most importantly,
Lee Jung and I created "WHERE YOU AT" choreography together.
But NaiN's taking it?
That makes no sense.
Honestly, I wanted her.
But...
Honestly, I need Lee Jung.
Okay.
- Really? - Of course.
I should make a concession,
so I can have Hee Su.
Hee Su is from my team.
She was the one I wanted to cast the most.
We talked about it...
and cast those we wanted.
Do you know what I wrote?
"Characteristics about the dancers you want: Someone like me."
(He loves himself so much.)
Honestly, I don't care about anything.
I just want to cast someone like me.
Let's go!
(Here's I am.)
(Already feeling lucky)
(Bothered)
(Cheering)
Yes. That's right!
Let's go!
That's scary.
(I love it.)
Let's go!
Where's she going?
(Flirting extremely)
(Fun to watch)
(Bonding by shouting)
(Excited)
Oh, my gosh.
(The sight of people trying to promote themselves)
(Look at me.)
That's right!
It was so chaotic.
(Getting heated up)
(Flirting together)
I loved it. I needed someone unique like them.
(Here comes waacking.)
(Here's voguing.)
(Promoting their genres)
That's right.
(A perfect finish)
(That's right!)
Yes. You got it.
(She really enjoyed it.)
- That was crazy. - I...
- Thank you. - Thank you.
"It's either this or nothing."
"I'm determined to do this."
I could feel that. I loved it.
That was dramatic.
That was crazy.
BABYZOO will be taking them all.
- That's what I mean. - Going first is...
At this rate...
What's NaiN going to do?
That's why it's important to go first.
Because I'm desperate...
We seemed to have the same concept...
from what I heard.
Let me tell you about my concept.
Like a jazz bar musical.
Like a party or a musical.
A duet as if a man and a woman are talking.
Divide the roles by gender.
To show diversity.
Hip-hop or girlish.
Hip-hop or jazz punk.
I knew it was going to overlap.
- NaiN. - Yes?
- Our concepts overlap, right? - But it's unavoidable...
- considering our songs. - Right.
They'll follow when you tell them to.
- And women walk here, right? - Yes.
But I prefer it that way.
I can make mine look better than hers.
I'm actually more confident.
In "RUDE!"...
(The intro begins as if they're on the phone.)
"You know what he said to me?"
They're talking to each other.
I decided to make it impactful by adding acting.
No choreography in the beginning.
You'll all be doing this.
You'll be on pause.
It's completely up to you, but I want everyone to be different.
Don't just do this.
(The practice begins.)
Your expression. Open your eyes wider.
Open your eyes wider.
(Like this!)
Half-heartedly without expression?
Never. I'm BABYZOO.
What's really important is the facial expression.
Yes. I need that.
We need a good facial expression...
to deliver the concept...
better.
Even if no one's looking at you, try to find someone.
You can scream and say, "Hey!"
"Look at me!"
I kept working on...
bringing out the dancers' talent.
Actually,
I want to give it a bigger impact,
and I had...
Gwacheon Honey Watermelon and Seung Min in mind.
They not only represent Gen Z,
but also receive a lot of support from Gen Z.
My team's weapon is the star quality,
so we might as well show our star quality.
Freestyle from here.
Freestyle here.
Let's go freestyle.
I'm telling them to spread their dreams.
The dancers I cast...
fly when they're given freedom.
That helps them express their characteristics.
I wanted to see their potential myself.
So I asked them to go freestyle.
There were so many moves...
that only BABYZOO could do.
Still, I need to...
make something new.
In terms of structure, I'm just as good.
If I come up with a good strategy, I might have a chance.
The intro upstairs.
Let me see it.
The song begins with a narration.
(NaiN's still working on the intro.)
Instead of doing the narration...
on the first floor,
I believe it'll draw more attention if I move it upstairs.
I plan to use the stage upstairs for the intro.
(Dancers' eyes and arms in all different directions)
Okay. You can look where your arms go.
For this part,
don't stretch your arms too wide.
Put your arms straight up.
A performance is all about details.
With a small number of people, it'll still look cool.
But with a large group...
How do you take your steps?
(The dancers move their feet at a different time.)
Imagine you're moving from the same spot.
Even when they're just standing,
keeping their toes straight or apart makes a big difference.
The details really matter.
It's NaiN versus BABYZOO.
It's BABYZOO.
I've never seen BABYZOO's performance before.
I'm looking forward to watching his the most.
Something cute...
and funny?
Acting, expression, skit.
He said acting is really important.
It's a good lineup.
"Showing the star quality."
Gwacheon Honey Watermelon and Seung Min are there too.
I wonder how he used New Jack Swing.
Let's watch BABYZOO's.
I'm sure he did a good job.
(BABYZOO's choreography practice)
(Starting with Gwacheon Honey Watermelon and Seung Min's acting)
Good job, Seung Min.
That's what he's good at.
When they go, "Wow,"
it's cute.
(In perfect sync)
It's making me happy.
I love how the outro unfolds.
I feel good watching it.
I feel good after watching it.
I'm curious about what NaiN did.
Okay.
One flow. Endless connection.
Convergence. Major flow.
She's forcing the idea that it's one flow.
Oh, not forcing.
(Not forcing, it's emphasizing.)
I wonder how it flows.
Let's go.
(NaiN's choreography practice)
(Focusing)
It's Hee Su.
I can tell it's Hee Su even in the distance.
Are they in the back?
Oh, they're upstairs.
They're upstairs.
(The intro takes place upstairs unlike BABYZOO.)
It's fun to watch.
They're good.
(Smiling)
She's cute.
Good job, NaiN.
(Approved)
(Clapping)
If I were the judge,
the result would be different.
There was a reason she emphasized it.
I like the flow.
The way she utilizes the stage.
They start upstairs.
Then they come downstairs to continue.
It looks like NaiN won.
NaiN's structure is definitely good.
Yes!
I can beat him.
(Confident about winning)
My performance has a better plot.
More people would vote for me.
BABYZOO versus NaiN?
The winner is BABYZOO.
Please.
I'm so nervous.
(Who is expected to win between BABYZOO and NaiN?)
(Really?)
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
Yes.
Oh, I'm so relieved.
That's what I really wanted.
To see my name up there.
It felt like they approved of me.
It felt great.
(Happy)
I lost. This is not good.
I was discouraged.
"It's okay to focus on one person from time to time."
"Not much directing."
"Lack of ideas or structure."
"Nothing impressive."
I remember things like, "Not much directing."
Since it's 40 people performing,
he could use more structure.
Twenty people would've been good enough for that performance.
In the section where the choreography changed...
(Switching to "WHERE YOU AT" from "RUDE!")
there was no structure to it.
It's a bummer how they just stand there and dance.
I didn't give much directing to it.
I get what they mean.
It's kind of too much to handle.
Because I know I'm not good enough.
(The mid-point review ends.)
Gosh.
If I know what my problem is, I want to fix it.
I'm curious.
There isn't much I could do on stage.
There's an entrance,
and there's something upstairs.
It got me thinking,
"Is my standard too low?"
Something about the structure...
I don't know.
I saw many comments about it.
(Sighing)
I don't know what to do.
What is wrong with me?
It's something I must overcome.
- Will I be able to overcome it? - Of course.
I must overcome it.
What can I do? It's a survival competition.
I can't lose like this.
Whether it's good or bad, take in all the comments.
I tend to...
keep going until I achieve the goal...
once I make up my mind.
I don't even need to sleep.
I kept working on it without going to bed.
- BABYZOO. - Yes?
You didn't leave until I left.
And you're here again.
(He never left the Directors' Room.)
I don't deserve to sleep.
What do you mean?
I must win.
I can never accept it.
I have to pull myself together...
and start over.
(The light in BABYZOO's Directors' Room remains on.)
Is anyone here?
(Spotting her prey)
(Startled)
BADA.
When are you going home?
I think I can turn it around today.
He thinks he can turn it around today.
- Show me. - I need a twist.
To win,
I can't help but change the current formation.
Sorry about that.
We'll have to change the highlight too.
But no major changes to the choreography.
So don't worry. Just make sure to follow my direction.
Let's speed up.
We don't have much time.
(BABYZOO checks the original choreography...)
(while practicing the new structure.)
(The dancers make a mistake due to the change in blocking.)
Hold on, everybody.
You can't get "RUDE!" wrong.
It's okay to get the new choreography wrong,
but I don't get why you're getting the original choreography wrong.
- Don't get it wrong. Okay? - Okay.
(Continuous choreography mistake due to the change in blocking)
(Moving at different times)
Wait, why are you getting that wrong?
Are they not paying attention?
They've been practicing the choreography for a while,
but they still haven't memorized it yet.
I'm really sorry, but it makes no sense.
Again.
Don't get it wrong. Please.
Please don't get it wrong.
Please. I'm begging you.
(Silence)
It's different. Is 0.5 correct?
(The dancers are confused of their positions.)
Everyone, focus.
(The dancers still look distracted.)
Do you want to do this 100 times?
(The air instantly freezes in the studio.)
Do it again.
It's disrespectful.
Am I not intimidating enough?
Let's do it again.
(Disciplined)
Why aren't you doing it when you can?
Why aren't you doing it?
I have to yell...
to make them follow me.
This is crazy. It's killing me.
Seriously.
I want to keep it fun.
It got me thinking if I didn't have what it takes to be a director.
I was really upset.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
I know it's too hard, right?
Sit down here.
- This is my first... - It's your first?
It's my first video.
So, honestly, I'm a little scared.
So I feel like...
"Hey. You can do more."
(BABYZOO had to go harsh on the dancers because he was scared.)
Yes. So...
I'm not angry, but...
you know what I mean?
I want it to be perfect and...
BABYZOO, you are really good.
You're a really nice teacher.
No, I can't say...
Trust me.
We're all happy to join your team.
I'm running out of time.
Today is my only chance.
That made me sensitive.
For that reason,
I should apologize to the dancers.
A lot of things changed today.
I'm sorry about that.
But I seriously think the new version is better.
I know it's confusing,
but please memorize the changes.
The thing about performance is,
you can give energy...
by pulling off your roles.
I know it's tough,
but please keep it up.
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Everyone was understanding.
We're perfect.
I checked every single detail...
to prevent any mistakes.
We didn't waste a single second.
(Team BABYZOO is actually monitoring together.)
Keep your hands up to the end.
The three of you. You'll have to practice all night with me.
(Adoring)
Team BABYZOO.
- Let's win! - Let's win!
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission BABYZOO versus NaiN)
Everyone, cheer up!
- Cheer up! - Cheer up!
Let's show them.
Yes!
I'm second to none when it comes to structure.
I'm confident.
Of course, I was bugged. She was right in front of me.
But I need to win.
You? You're no match for me.
I'll put my name on the Director Credit.
- I can't lose. - Me neither.
I can't lose either.
(Tension rises between two teams.)
Don't touch me.
- Okay. - So seniority...
doesn't even matter anymore, does it?
- We'll see about that. - Okay. I get it.
I love it.
- BABYZOO. - Jo Na In.
- BABYZOO. - BABYZOO.
- Jo Na In. - Jo Na In.
- BABYZOO. - I can do even better.
I think I have a chance.
BABYZOO versus NaiN.
We'll now begin their Last Run.
BABYZOO, during this mission,
do you think you can decide who's more superior...
after this performance?
Yes, I'm very confident.
(The Last Run is all about confidence.)
I couldn't be more confident.
Because I lost the mid-point review,
I changed it...
by adding more wow factors.
I can win.
I'll take the Director Credit.
Let's go!
- Yes! - Yes!
(Team BABYZOO is filled with energy.)
What I'm most worried about is the energy.
We won't know until they do it, right?
Yes, we'll have to see.
I think a director's capability is...
the forest.
That'd be the highlight.
You know what's interesting about BABYZOO?
With his bangs down, he's a choreographer.
With his bangs up, he becomes a battler.
They're slightly up today, so he's a slight battler today.
My performance will be better than NaiN's.
I changed the choreography...
by adding more wow factors.
I strongly believe that I'll receive a good response.
I'm sure I'll win.
Now, let's begin BABYZOO's Last Run.
Ready, fight.
Yes! This is going to be fun!
I can't wait.
("Our Spectrum")
(Choreographer of the signature part of "RUDE!": BABYZOO)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "WHERE YOU AT": BABYZOO)
(Performance by Team BABYZOO)
("RUDE!" by Hearts2Hearts, "WHERE YOU AT" by ALLDAY PROJECT)
He's so cute.
- Wait. That's Watermelon. - It's Watermelon.
(Happy)
(Glancing)
I love that start.
Look at his energy.
It's intense.
Let's go.
(BABYJOO's signature choreography part in "RUDE!")
Let's go!
It's so neat.
He did a good job of utilizing the dancers.
He's good.
So cute.
He's really good.
(Falling for "RUDE!")
It looks like a musical.
(Happy)
They had good energy.
They kind of made me nervous.
That's so cute.
Can you believe that energy?
That's so cute. Nice.
Yes.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
I love this part.
They're in perfect sync.
(Crazy chemistry)
It's Lee Jung.
Yes. We need that.
(BABYJOO's signature choreography part in "WHERE YOU AT")
His movements are already perfect.
He has Lee Jung.
Let's go.
(Cheering)
(Eyes focused)
It's so neat.
She's the queen.
He really utilized the stage.
He changed it to New Jack Swing.
Nice.
It looks like an old club.
It's giving me the chills.
(Immersed)
It's really impactful.
That's so cool.
It's different.
I love that vibe.
It's a happy performance. So happy.
That's so cool.
- It's unbelievable. - It feels like a party.
Come on.
It's a nice formation.
I like how it's not ordinary New Jack Swing.
The light work is crazy.
That's crazy.
That's insane.
(Team BABYZOO's dancers)
So cool.
(BABYZOO's Last Run ends.)
I need to throw my shoes.
(Approved)
He nailed it.
The outfits, color,
and the vibe. It's perfect.
"I got it."
"I think I did it."
I knew my structure would work.
He really gritted his teeth.
I'm kind of nervous.
You can do it!
Very exciting.
I think NaiN's is neater.
NaiN's performance was new.
BABYZOO made a lot of changes.
I also created a performance...
with my own interpretation.
I'll show you what I've got.
(What kind of performance did NaiN prepare?)
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Can you please stand in the starting formation?
NaiN is the new rising choreographer.
I'm looking forward to seeing her.
I scheduled it.
I'll first check the choreography.
Then I'll check the light.
If everything's okay, we'll practice to the music.
She wrote down the lights in detail.
It changes every four bars.
Every four bars.
Both their concepts are...
a dance carnival.
The song probably influenced...
their concepts.
Then they should've come up with something else for it.
It won't be in my favor if we go in the same direction.
Since it's a New Jack Swing song,
I decided to go with hip-hop.
HANYA, please get ready.
She has many hip-hop dancers.
If she's going to use HANYA, hip-hop is perfect.
Nice vibe.
They're really great hip-hop dancers.
They're a very cheerful team.
Hip-hop will be the base...
and the key to this performance.
They're good. They're really good.
They're good dancers.
That's crazy.
Good job, HANYA.
Let's practice "RUDE!" formation again.
- One, two, three, four... - They should be in sync.
It's a matter...
of how perfect the director makes it.
One, two, three, four. Again.
- One, two, three... - She's so precise.
Again. One...
Can you move forward?
Can you move back?
Move forward.
The angle of your body is important.
- About this much. - Okay.
She's checking meticulously.
- It's all up to the dancers. - Yes.
Let's try that again.
Okay.
(The dancers are in perfect sync after fixing the details.)
It's better than before.
Wow factors don't just come from novelty.
They also come from being perfect.
That's what gives one potential.
I believe a performance is not completed...
until it's presented on stage.
I'm going to keep trying to make the best of what I have.
I'll do my best...
to put my name on the Director Credit.
Now, it's time for NaiN's Last Run.
- Are you ready? - Yes.
I can never lose.
You're no match for me.
My name should be on it.
Ready, fight.
It'll depend on how she utilized HANYA.
I think she's the first one to start upstairs.
I think it will be important to trust my team members.
I'm going to dance the hardest I ever have in my life.
I have to win.
(Resonance: Energy Connecting the City)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Rude!": BABYZOO)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Where You At!": BABYZOO)
It's starting from the second floor?
It's Hee Su.
She's so cute.
Bring it on if you dare.
Her presence is unmistakable.
It looks like "MAMA."
(BABYZOO's signature choreography part in "Rude!")
- Okay. - This is nice.
It's still the same as rehearsal.
This is just so NaiN.
Why is it so clean?
- It's clean versus clean. - I know.
It's really precise.
She's cute.
Gosh, seriously...
The structure is well put together.
She dances so well.
I love it.
It looks so pretty.
They're so well in sync.
(Satisfied)
(Focused)
Look at the lines when their arms drop.
Weren't they all originally on the same team or something?
HANYA is coming out.
Gosh. HANYA!
This is way better.
So she made this part into a couple dance.
(BABYZOO's signature choreography part in "Where You At")
The pair work is great.
This is how they choreographed it.
This is so cool.
It's so clean.
The synergy is remarkable.
It's really clean.
This is insane.
The formation is spotless.
Great sense of depth.
It's because they dance so well.
I was quite surprised.
I think this structure is solid.
They planned out the strategy so well.
It looks even cooler seeing it up close.
It's amazing. I love it already.
The vibe is so good.
I think HANYA is going to tear it up again with the New Jack Swing.
(Cheering)
They're so talented.
They are seriously so good.
(This is insane.)
It's amazing.
It's so nice to watch, and it just makes me happy.
The dancing is solid.
It was quite threatening.
They're so good.
It feels refreshing.
The formation layout is interesting.
(In awe)
I don't know how the results will turn out.
Building the pathway with the dancers is a masterstroke.
(Team Nain Dancers: Hee Su, Mooreup, WISE, ROOT, Enrique, Arthur, Denny)
- Great. - Okay.
(Watch the comparison video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
(That was so cool.)
They did so well.
I feel so relieved.
There isn't anything I regret.
I feel like I'm going to win.
This team will win.
My personal pick is NaiN.
Really?
She brought out...
- It was so good! - the New Jack Swing so well.
- She pulled it off well. - Yes.
It's definitely BABYZOO.
NaiN's performance had formations you could already anticipate.
This one is tough.
Will both choreographers please step onto the stage?
I'm sure that I will win.
I'm confident.
(Confident)
I don't know.
(The face-off of rookie directors, BABYZOO versus NaiN)
That's crazy.
That was crazy.
I think these are probably...
the two best shows I've seen tonight so far.
(Agreed)
Let's go!
(Thank you.)
I think I finally understand now.
Why BABYZOO and Nain are getting...
so much work these days.
(Nodding in agreement)
This is why the industry calls them up.
And they each carry distinct colors.
They listened to the same track and took on the same concept,
but their choices were different, which made it a thrilling battle.
It felt like watching two entertaining movies.
BABYZOO's film...
was like a teen movie...
where you could imagine the plot, maybe even with a touch of romance.
(BABYZOO's performance evokes a teen movie with a narrative.)
And NaiN's film felt like "Step Up."
It felt like watching a crisp, exhilarating dance movie...
speaking powerfully through pure dance.
Isn't "Step Up..."
way cooler, though?
What I was aiming for in the performance...
seemed to come across clearly,
so it felt great.
First off, what impressed me most...
when watching BABYZOO's performance...
was the strong impression of seasoned experience.
I think it was a clever choice to structurally dictate...
what to watch,
using the lighting to guide the eyes...
like saying, "Look right here."
In contrast to BABYZOO, NaiN utilized...
a wide variety of dynamic formations,
and I thought those visual pictures were stunning...
and brilliantly staged.
I comfortably enjoyed...
those diverse, "Step Up" -style visuals.
I had a lot of fun.
I think I'm going to win.
Seeing the judges' reactions,
I suddenly felt uneasy.
NaiN.
I think you're the smartest person in the room.
(Thank you.)
With the second song, when you started having the guys dance,
it wasn't like individuals. Everybody was like one group.
(Spotless synchronization stood out even in the pair choreography.)
I don't want to say because you're young, that's amazing.
I think you're just amazing.
I choked up a little.
He recognized my capabilities regardless of my age.
I was really grateful.
I'm in trouble.
Honestly, I needed to win, so I felt pretty anxious.
I really think she was like,
ten out of ten.
And in the case of BABYZOO's movements,
while using the rhythm and energy of New Jack Swing,
I think he interpreted the moves in a far more contemporary way.
The reaction was so positive...
that I believe I can win this.
But I'm confident.
Because I made a better piece.
The 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
Who will be the choreographer to showcase their work...
to the audience and put their name...
on the credit board?
We're revealing it now.
- BABYZOO! - BABYZOO!
It's definitely BABYZOO.
NaiN had that more polished...
and cleaner feel.
Having the male and female dancers battle was also a masterstroke.
BABYZOO versus NaiN.
NaiN versus BABYZOO.
The choreographer who will claim their name on the credit board...
as Director is...
I need to take the Director Credit for myself.
I'm so confident.
It will be mine for sure.
The winner is...
When is the result popping up?
When is it popping up?
Orange.
I have to win.
I'm really confident.
The choreographer who will claim their name on the credit board...
as Director is...
It is BABYZOO!
(BABYZOO wins.)
(BABYZOO gets his name on the Director Credit.)
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
Great work, NaiN.
- BABYZOO! - BABYZOO!
We made it.
I was so happy.
In terms of directing ability,
BABYZOO utilized the members...
in such a diverse way.
It was so powerful that it genuinely moved me.
So I think I'll be casting my vote for BABYZOO.
The scope...
of BABYZOO's direction was broader.
He dialed in every detail...
- of the acting. - Exactly.
So in terms of directing capability, BABYZOO seems to have the edge.
I really think she was like, 10 out of 10.
I think it's just unfortunate.
He's like 11 out of 10.
Even though it was BABYZOO's piece,
he worked the magic of making the other characters...
come alive even more.
Because it was a performance...
where the staging technique shone through the dancers' utilization,
I have high hopes that another fantastic director...
has been born.
I really enjoyed it.
I felt even better...
because it seemed like the judges fully understood...
everything I wanted to express.
- BABYZOO! - BABYZOO!
This is what I told the dancers.
"Let's create just one scene where we look..."
"the happiest and most joyful,"
"making everyone who watches want to dance along."
It was probably tough in the beginning...
with the rocky moments and endless revisions.
Still, they trusted me and followed my lead no matter what.
So I want to thank them again.
They told me, "You're the best director."
You're a really nice teacher.
I don't think you could have done any better than this.
I'm so grateful and happy.
Team BABYZOO!
- Let's win! - It was so wonderful...
working with those dancers.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
In the end, BABYZOO was the only choreographer...
who succeeded in leaving his name on this stage...
until the very end.
- BABYZOO! - BABYZOO!
- You did great. - Jo Na In!
- Jo Na In! - Jo Na In!
It's so disappointing. It was...
such a back-and-forth battle all the way to the Last Run,
so I think it came down to the slimmest margin.
I felt so bad for the dancers.
We prepared so hard,
so it's a shame that we can't showcase it to the audience.
Thinking that I should have led them better...
brought up mixed emotions.
I'm going to win in the next mission...
to honor all the sweat you shed for me,
so I hope we can keep cheering each other on...
and just enjoy dancing together.
- Thank you. - Good luck!
I sincerely hope that the day will come...
when I, too, can show my piece.
I needed a catalyst to recharge that fierce fire inside me,
which made me want to win...
even more in the next mission.
BADA versus INGYOO.
(INGYOO's new "Smoke" performance)
(BADA's new Like Jennie performance)
(The result of the signature choreography takeover match)
(INGYOO won.)
I protected my own choreography...
while snatching BADA's away.
It feels great
(Chuckling)
BADA's mental state is probably completely shattered.
The most crucial thing is not letting myself get swept up in it.
Since I got the first button right just the way I wanted,
I have to carry the momentum all the way through.
This was the very first mission...
where my performance was being showcased.
But having failed to secure the credit,
I wondered if this was really all I amounted to.
What is it that I can show through this mission?
Can I look at the evaluations?
How the choreographers evaluated me.
Could I just see the shortcomings?
(They mostly pointed out repetitive choreography...)
(and a lack of focal points.)
It's shocking.
(Punching)
(Groaning)
This makes me feel better.
It's sad, but what can I do? I just have to push through.
My biggest objective right now is...
to thoroughly study my weaknesses,
quickly identify what I urgently need,
and prepare for the next battle.
This is what makes it fun. It fuels my competitive drive.
It's not over until it's over.
To take the Director Credit, I really need to do this right.
Hello!
(Team BADA Practice Room)
So we kicked off our first rehearsal.
I lost my signature choreography for this round.
Everyone, isn't this amazing?
- Yes! - Isn't it great?
Don't you think we can pull off an insanely cool performance?
- Yes! - Yes!
So for this signature part,
we'll be doing INGYOO's signature choreography.
The dancers' expressions looked disappointed and worried.
So I thought I should build their trust in me.
(INGYOO visited Team BADA for the choreography handover.)
When Ingyoo was teaching,
I took the lead even more.
I think you need to step forward a bit.
Do you want to run it from the top once...
- and then listen to the track? - Okay.
I deliberately spoke extra loudly toward INGYOO.
- From the top... - Check the line change later.
It did get on my nerves.
A fire was blazing inside my mind.
But getting emotionally hung up on that...
wouldn't get me anywhere, so I figured I should do my job.
I wanted to memorize INGYOO's piece as fast as possible...
so I could teach it to my team myself.
So I went out of my way to step to the back...
and teach them more.
It should go right away.
(BADA completely took over the teaching zone.)
(And INGYOO watched the situation.)
I tried to take over the room's momentum.
(Before anyone realized it, BADA gained the upper hand.)
This is interesting.
(There you go!)
(What is going on?)
This is really funny.
I could feel BADA getting all competitive in real time.
Right then, I went...
(What?)
We got all fired up.
It sparked her competitive spirit. It was scary.
But even so, I thought...
I could beat BADA once we hit the stage.
The dancers are going to struggle with INGYOO's choreography.
Pulling off this rhythm with swagger is going to be difficult for them.
My choreography isn't on the easy side,
even if it might look it.
While the focal design points are set,
I give freedom to the movements.
Okay!
I needed a lot of dancers who could deliver that vibe,
so I called in WE DEM BOYZ.
Go!
They all shine brightly.
(INGYOO's hidden trump card: WE DEM BOYZ)
Having WE DEM BOYZ there was such a huge relief.
Say, "Oh!"
The pure satisfaction hit immediately.
It felt like doing what we were meant to do.
(This is it!)
(Completely absorbing INGYOO's signature style)
Taking the Director Credit with my choreography...
is going to be pretty tough.
I know it will be tough.
It's not my choreography, so I put a lot of thought into it.
If some dancers find the execution too difficult,
I plan to resolve it through blocking and formations,
so not everyone needs to perform the moves.
And my concept was crystal clear right from the start.
My concept is a runway.
A stable, cool performance.
Because the visual picture I wanted to show was so clear,
I even held meetings on how to direct the lighting.
If you want silhouette lighting tailored to the positions...
Also, in the process of turning the runway...
into a mega crew scale,
I tried to incorporate varied visual pictures.
For instance, like diagonal entrances...
or walking out to stage a confrontation showdown,
I made an effort to add twist elements.
And I tried...
to utilize plenty of props and objects.
All these circumstances worked in my favor.
So I think I can win this.
BADA says she's going with a runway concept.
But isn't this a game...
where you can just dress sharp and let the dance speak for itself?
I can pack so much into the choreography,
so formations aren't all that crucial to me.
The choreography has such great flavor...
that the dance alone will keep all eyes glued to the stage.
So I sorted out the dancers...
capable of pulling off my choreography.
Even while the other team was mapping out blockings,
I chose to focus...
and take my time drilling the choreo.
It looks like we need to run this a few more times.
(Day 4 of Choreography Practice)
Dance quality was my number one priority.
So I allocated more time to drilling the choreography.
Even so, there were dancers...
who still fell short of the required level.
She was someone who lacked even the fundamentals of execution.
She simply couldn't execute the movements at all.
Her learning pace...
was noticeably slow.
I'm worried about whether she can pull this off.
Is there a part you can't pull off?
I think you need to ask questions.
(Staring)
Is everything all right?
Flip it like this. Like turning the page of a book.
(Grooving)
What should I do?
She just couldn't dance.
I look like a stick.
- You're like a stick? - Yes.
Keep at it and you'll get it.
(Stiff)
Yes. Like that.
Even after giving her one-on-one tutoring,
correcting the moves seems tough,
so I'm a bit concerned.
A few of the dancers were looking hopeless.
I've never prepared a performance...
with dancers like this before,
so I'm not sure I can put this on stage. This is serious.
You two, please step forward.
(INGYOO calls out specific dancers.)
(Esma)
(Among them, Esma is called out as well.)
The dancers I just picked are going to hold the cloth.
You'll be holding a red sheet of cloth.
It was my own strategy.
Keeping the dancers who can't pull off the moves out of sight.
(Immediately starting practice for raising the cloth)
Seven, eight.
Two, three, four.
(In the middle of practice, Esma suddenly sits down.)
What was that?
She suddenly sat on the floor.
(Refusing to budge)
Cool.
(Dropping her head)
(He spotted her.)
What's wrong?
What is it?
(Flustered)
(Tension suddenly envelops the practice room.)
She says she wants to know if she has...
- any more choreo parts. - What?
I don't want to know.
(I don't want to know.)
Oh, my goodness.
Are you good?
(In the end)
(Esma storms out of the practice room.)
Okay.
Let's take a short break.
What was that?
What? What's wrong?
They are...
questioning why they aren't in the actual dance parts.
I'm doing this...
because I want to give everyone as much of a role as possible, too.
I can't cater to every single one of them.
That sounds like some utopian, politically correct fantasy.
I'm sorry, but this is a survival show.
It doesn't make sense.
This is a competition where I must put skilled dancers front...
to grab the spotlight if I want to win.
I made the choice I had to make.
- I have something I'd like to ask. - Okay.
I want to hear what my issue was...
and what I was lacking.
(During the twerking part audition held today)
These are the selected dancers.
Thank you.
(Esma was left unpicked.)
I wanted to pick dancers with stable execution,
but you kept rushing the tempo.
- We only practiced for 15 minutes. - I know.
- And since I was in the back... - I know.
- I can't nail it right away. - I know.
I need practice.
The actual performance is coming up soon.
So I wanted to pick dancers who wouldn't mess up.
I won't mess up.
But there are too many dancers here for me...
to accommodate everyone's personal circumstances.
I have to look out for the other dancers as well.
There's barely any time left.
I needed someone I could lock in with certainty.
This isn't just a show. It's a competition.
If I don't do this right, I get eliminated right away.
That's why.
It can't be helped.
I'm sorry, but it is what it is.
It breaks my heart too. I have to cut off many people here.
Every time I see them watching me from behind,
it tears me apart.
They have to dance. They have to do something too.
I felt sorry for the dancers.
They must've expected to perform on stage.
I'd appreciate it if you understand how I feel.
I understand how you feel.
You must feel hurt and disappointed.
But...
I hope you will keep your spirits up.
(INGYOO offers a handshake.)
How can I neglect her when we're in it together?
We have to go together.
I want you to try harder tomorrow...
and perform well on stage.
As a director, I need to accept them and lead them.
It's what a director must do.
I'm curious about BADA.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission Interim Review Day)
"1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission practice video."
"Please predict the winner of each matchup..."
"and who the winning director will be."
Oh, my gosh!
(Here it is.)
I'm already excited.
It's such a big match that I can't possibly predict...
who's going to win.
Should I watch it?
Can't wait to watch it.
Gosh.
I love it.
Vata is too good.
This is unfair.
He's too good.
(Vata is on another level.)
There it is.
(Signature choreography part in "like JENNIE")
(In sync)
Staying true to the original.
It's fun that INGYOO not Jennie, is in the center,
when it's "like JENNIE."
(Clapping)
He's too good. This is unfair.
His dance is too good.
I think he really captured the appeal...
and energy of a mega crew.
BADA!
Additional casting. Goodness.
Audrey?
Is this Audrey that Audrey?
(Team BADA's key dancer is Audrey.)
JAM REPUBLIC's Audrey.
(JAM REPUBLIC's standout youngest member)
Audrey is unbelievable.
How did she get her? I'm surprised.
Scary.
The synopsis was a runway featuring people of various nationalities.
I wonder how she interpreted it. It must have been challenging.
To carry that concept all the way through.
I bet BADA really brought her A-game.
I’m going to prove I can pull off a mega crew performance.
Let's see.
They’re coming out strong from the start.
They are using a lot of props.
The one in blue is so good.
It's Audrey.
Audrey is really carrying the team.
Ay!
The choreography is superb.
BADA's strength is...
choreography.
I think she composed it well,
in her style.
Then the smoke came out with a whoosh.
It matched the sound so perfectly.
It was like magic.
Gosh, BADA.
She clearly used the dancers...
to build these visual formations.
But it still feels...
a little unpolished.
There’s a lot of moving in and out.
It feels a little chaotic.
They're the opposite.
BADA put emphasis on the overall composition.
INGYOO's performance is all about being wild.
I think it's about the difference in their strategies.
I can't see it.
Even if it's still a bit rough,
I hope they will look at the artistry of it...
or the varied composition.
At the end of the day,
my dance has so much appeal,
so I think I will win.
It's hard to tell.
(BADA versus INGYOO. Which director is most likely to win?)
Gosh.
Yes!
It felt so good.
I was very sad.
Why am I here?
I had my choreography stolen already.
Hearing that assessment,
I felt like I've been pushed out into the middle of nowhere.
(Laughing)
BADA can't laugh.
It must be frustrating...
and very painful.
This is hard.
At this point, there's no turning back.
She could add to it, but...
I don't know. Will it be able to turn out well?
I think it will be very tough.
Don't tell me everyone picked INGYOO.
(INGYOO)
No way.
I didn't think it would be so extreme.
I expected to get at least two votes.
This happened on "Street Woman Fighter 2" too.
I started getting very anxious.
"The overall composition and quality are not good enough."
"The intent of the synopsis doesn't come through clearly."
Because the dancers aren't moving in sync as they move in and out,
it feels a little distracting.
The comments were not something I expected.
It made me think about how I should fix it.
I felt a bit lost.
You know that first judgement.
There's someone who doesn't come across as a director.
It felt as if that was becoming true,
and I was scared.
The rehearsal began. Please focus.
He's INGYOO?
Yes.
No, it's my first time to see him without the glasses.
We'll run "Smoke" using vocal counts.
(INGYOO stole BADA's signature "Smoke.")
BADA must be sad. He stole it from her.
(He had fun making it, but he succeeded to steal it.)
It's perfectly INGYOO's vibe.
He has a really good sense of rhythm.
He interpreted "Smoke" with such tight, punchy movements.
He choreographed it so well.
The stage concept is raiders in a wasteland.
It has this Mad Max vibe where things get increasingly brutal...
until it ends in death.
INGYOO I see...
gets completely immersed in the dance...
through that vibe and emotion.
But I don't think storytelling is one of his strengths.
I want to see how he's going to show this concept.
I chose to focus on what mattered most.
While BADA focused on composition...
I don't care too much about the composition.
I want my choreography to be so good...
that people can't take their eyes off of it.
I want people to get immersed.
It has to look cool at first glance.
I want to keep it sharp.
Grace, can you stand for me?
(Dancer Grace)
She's a voguing dancer.
Grace was supposed to be the focal point.
The spotlight should be pinned here.
Can you pin the spotlight to where she is standing?
She has to stand out. Yes.
It would be nice if the circle is smaller.
Grace is a rising dancer.
People love her because she's stylish.
She makes the dance fashionable.
It looks like he designed it to look iconic.
What are they going to do?
Should we try it? 6, 7, 8.
(Attention-grabbing)
So that's the scorpion concept.
It's very unique.
It pleases the eyes.
I'm curious.
I focused on gradually building up the scale...
with colorful, dynamic visuals.
He's got a clear picture.
Taking the hype to the next level.
Gosh, it's crazy!
Let's go!
I have conviction.
This is the winning direction.
You will be overwhelmed.
BADA versus INGYOO. Last Run will begin.
- Are you ready? - Yes!
Ready, 3, 2, 1!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
It was a worship ritual to make the world dance.
(Shouting)
Let's go!
- Just do as we prepared. - Yes.
You don't need anything else. Just do as you prepared.
I put a lot of thought into making the performance feel...
both solid and dynamic.
(Team INGYOO goes.)
I'm not afraid to go head-to-head when it comes to directing.
Hey!
I have a better physique,
so I think I have an upper hand.
I guess we will be competing physically.
But I don't think that will be an issue.
It's over.
(She can't believe it.)
- Hey. - Hey.
Hey.
I try not to care,
but it didn't feel good.
Tie your shoelaces and drawstrings.
Let's double-knot your shoelaces.
Make sure to zip our pants.
You're copying me.
Why does he keep provoking me? It's childish.
I will win.
You think you will win?
I will beat INGYOO.
Team BADA. Team INGYOO.
Please enter the set with your dancers.
(Both teams enter the set.)
Let's go!
- Please. - Why am I so nervous?
This is crazy.
(Everyone is in.)
One, two, three. Make some noise!
(Shouting)
I didn't ask them to say "Ooh! Ooh!"
But they still did it. It means we've become one team.
Choreographers, please enter the stage.
- BADA! - BADA!
(Making a strong first impression with cheers)
INGYOO is great!
(We can't lose.)
I want to win for my teammates.
- I am not worried about my team. - INGYOO!
BADA!
They're copying us again.
(Serious face)
What's that?
(Provoking them)
- What? - Is that cool?
The tension between the dancers is intense, too.
You can tell everyone is fully invested in this performance.
This is going to be really fun.
It's really fun.
Personally, I admire and love...
both directors, BADA and INGYOO.
It feels like the fight between water and fire.
Can you say something to each other before the match?
Since INGYOO took my signature choreography,
I need to take that gold credit.
I believe it's now my turn to win.
Why don’t you fire things up your own way, too?
Anything I want to say to her?
Go, BADA!
- Go, BADA! - Go, BADA!
There's no need to be wordy.
That's how confident I was.
It's the leader versus leader.
So I knew it was going to be fun.
Honestly, I think INGYOO will win.
I think the choreography perfectly brings all three elements together.
BADA’s determination must be going through the roof.
I'm sorry, INGYOO, but I'm on BADA's side.
I'm ready to draw my sword.
I am determined to win.
Good luck, BADA.
But the "director" title is mine.
BADA's here,
but they've got Vata.
This is a big match. Truly.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
WE DEM BOYZ has that incredible freshness.
The quality of the choreography was too good.
And I felt threatened.
A choreography powerhouse.
How can INGYOO manage to be relaxed all the time?
INGYOO stole her choreography, you know.
I'm not worried. I'm convinced.
Feel our energy!
It's time for INGYOO's Last Run.
Ready, fight!
- I need to watch this. - I'm curious.
I'm excited.
(Nervous)
(The Pyre)
(A lawless wasteland where raw energy and freedom collide.)
(Dynamic movement builds tension to a fiery climax.)
What is this?
So scary!
(Performance by Team INGYOO)
It's WE DEM BOYZ.
Nice vibe.
(Curious)
I can't wait to watch it.
(Staring intensely)
(INGYOO's new signature choreography part in "Smoke")
That's it.
(Thrilled)
It's too good.
Look at that quality.
The dance is unbelievable.
WE DEM BOYZ is truly...
Like hyenas.
They're good.
- There he is. - Is he Vata?
They are too good.
Goodness, Vata.
This is wild.
- The choreography is so fun. - I didn't know someone could...
dance "Smoke" with such tight, punchy movements.
He came up with the most incredible choreography.
I tried to stay calm.
- Is it Grace? - It's Grace.
I love it.
Oh, my gosh!
The concept is a scorpion.
It's mad. She's like a sculpture.
Incredible use of character.
She's good.
I love her so much.
She's like a model.
She's a cool woman.
This is mad, isn't it?
She's incredible.
- What is it? - What is it?
Why are they bringing out the cloth?
There they are.
(Cheering)
Love the vibe of the dancer in the center.
I love her.
She's so sexy!
Too fast. She didn't match the music.
There he comes.
Let's go.
- He has to come out. - Signature.
That's it!
(INGYOO's new signature choreography part in "like JENNIE")
Okay, let's go!
Yes!
(So much thrill!)
It's INGYOO, not Jennie.
Isn't this choreography too good to be true?
Crazy.
This is mad.
He must be a genius.
I love the choreography.
(Amazed)
INGYOO is super relaxed.
It's nothing new, so I didn't mind it.
Is he crazy?
He's too cool.
He's got a great sense of rhythm.
(Gasping)
What is this?
Too trendy.
Look at that!
No way.
(The crowd goes wild!)
INGYOO really made it his own.
INGYOO is mad.
It's perfectly his. He plays it so well.
(Shocked)
(Attention-grabbed)
Wild.
No way.
There's fire too?
There are lots of exciting elements.
Vata is crazy.
How can they dance so well?
Let's go!
That's it!
(Going crazy)
They are so good.
(Watching closely)
- The quality is mad. - That's it!
They dance so tastefully.
So cool.
I approve them.
He must be a genius.
(Team INGYOO Dancers)
(Oh!)
(Clapping)
(They killed it.)
Look at the ending.
That was fire.
He made clever use of those devices.
The moves hit so hard.
(Mesmerized by the dance)
With Vata, it's so tight.
He's going to have a landslide victory.
I can clearly tell he won.
(The heat doesn't go away even after the performance ends.)
I tried my best to put my heart into the performance...
so the dancers and I can have fun.
Watching that made me more confident.
We pulled out all the stops.
I think we will do better.
We will do better.
Team BADA, let's go.
Huge hardships had hit me.
I am desperate to prove myself...
as a director.
I thought very hard about in which direction...
I should be leading this performance.
Can I watch INGYOO's one more time?
INGYOO is my opponent.
What's the reason?
(Why did he win?)
Can I watch INGYOO's one more time?
Can I watch it once more?
I want to watch INGYOO's one more time.
I watched INGYOO's practice video many times.
After watching the video, I realized this.
There is a lot of simple moves.
He likes simple moves.
That's what I learned.
When I watched the rehearsals,
I thought the performance of the directors who play...
a bigger role as a player felt a little fuller.
And they were the ones who won more often.
I actually thought the opposite.
I thought of myself as a director,
not a dancer.
So when I watched it,
I realized that I was missing my emotions.
If I increase my involvement, my energy,
and my value as a player,
wouldn't my performance get better?
I'll lose the moves I need to lose.
I took time to rethink about performances...
and made a list of adjustments I need to make.
That's what I tried to do.
You surprised me.
Aren't you tired?
Tomorrow is the last day.
But I got a disappointing result.
Yes, you are a director,
but you are a player too.
INGYOO has Vata as the lead player.
But imagine he loses Vata.
It will feel different.
Where you place yourself is your call.
I believe you have enough potential.
BADA, you are the strongest when you are on stage.
You have hope.
Hearing those things made me realize that I still have hope.
I am going to give my all as a player too.
(Blocking Rehearsal D-1)
People predicted that INGYOO is more likely to win.
What?
With that in mind, I'm going to make...
several adjustments quickly.
The dancers who come in here...
You won't be coming in at first. I will dance alone.
At first, I didn't want to perform.
But I thought I would direct myself.
I know so well what I'm good at.
I can utilize myself however I want.
I knew I had to do it. I had to convince them.
I put the most effort...
into my own runway.
I wanted this part to be performed by someone...
with impact, weight, and aura.
Who could it be?
I should do it. That's who I am.
I am the hero of this stage.
So I put myself there.
(BADA utilized her strength and added her part.)
She's great.
I became more and more convinced.
Hello.
- It's BADA. - BADA is...
such an icon.
She should make quite an impact.
I am hoping for it.
The countdown began.
When you do the moves on the second floor...
I had to get everything sorted in just 80 minutes.
I had to look at the harmony of the dancers,
the dance, the lights, and the prop utilization.
It's going to be very tight.
Did everyone check their paths on the sides?
Okay. Second floor. Checked?
- Yes. - Okay.
Those throwing the cloth.
You shouldn't be throwing it to the path. Got it?
- Yes. - Okay.
She's checking the major formations and movement paths.
I think she's picking out the points and checking them.
I love it. So simple.
Let's try the runway formation.
I needed to sell the runway idea to them.
I tried incorporating a more linear formation.
We also need to coordinate the runway lighting.
I put a lot of effort into the lighting.
Great.
Because it's a runaway, the lights are linear too.
If people who have no idea see it and think, "It's a runway,"
it means it worked. It means she sold the idea.
Okay. Should we go here?
- Okay. - The pyramid formation.
Yes. There.
- Audrey? - From "Street Woman Fighter?"
I like her.
Audrey's got that energy and cleanliness.
I will put her in the center...
and improve the quality of the performance.
I love her character utilization.
As a director, BADA is much more relaxed now.
I think BADA is going to do the run-through.
Ready?
Okay. Should we perform to the music then?
So BADA is going to be in the center.
(BADA, the player, enters the stage.)
It's BADA versus INGYOO.
So she's doing the dance Team INGYOO did.
That would hurt my pride.
I lost "Smoke" choreography to him.
So I wanted to do it myself.
I wanted to show him that this is how I perform...
"Smoke."
It feels completely different.
Once the center is firmly established,
it makes the wings feel like they're spreading wide.
She made it work. She made it different.
- BADA made it her own. - Yes.
That's what you call talent.
She's so good.
That's how you lead!
She's both a player and a director.
As a player, you have to really crank up...
the physical energy to focus on the play.
As a director, you need to use your brain. So it's different.
BADA is such a well-rounded person.
- That's really incredible. - I respect her for it.
Okay!
- Well done, everyone! - Well done.
Things aren't going too smoothly for me right now.
The most important thing is...
that I want to perform without regrets.
We got this. Let's give a big shout before we start.
One, two, three!
(Shout!)
(Let's go, Team BADA!)
Let's show them!
I'm looking forward to her performance.
I did everything I could.
We'll show them...
what our runway looks like.
I'm not really worried.
I think I'll win.
Ready.
Fight.
It's going to be cool.
(Choreographer of the signature part of "Smoke": INGYOO)
(Choreographer of the signature part of "like JENNIE": INGYOO)
She planned something.
- What's that? - She's using clothes.
Is it like an exhibition?
I'm curious.
("Smoke" by Dynamic Duo and Lee Young Ji)
(INGYOO's ne signature choreography part in "Smoke")
Look at the power.
(Surprised)
This is what I wanted to see.
Yes, BADA is essential.
Her power.
This is impossible.
(This is it.)
(Nervous)
(Smoke appears.)
What's that?
That's so cool.
She's so good.
She's a one-man army.
I love it.
Her moves are so cool.
(As expected of BADA.)
She's impressive.
BADA is essential for the performance.
The lighting's pretty.
It's Audrey.
She's so good.
She's such a good dancer.
She has an awesome vibe.
(Amazed)
She's so cool.
- What's that? - What's that?
Who is that?
(Worried)
What's this?
She made a story of her own.
I love this.
This is crazy.
This is what I call a mega crew performance.
Nice.
She changed everything.
Hey.
(She loves it.)
So cool.
My gosh.
He's impossible.
(INGYOO's ne signature choreography part in "like JENNIE")
Look at his physique.
He's so good.
My gosh.
He has a killer vibe.
It's so cool.
Oh, my gosh.
I love this part.
She developed it a lot.
I like this. A runway.
Come on!
She has a killer vibe.
This is crazy.
It's Jennie.
(A very passionate...)
(performance)
So cool.
Let's go!
This part is done so well.
This choreography is good.
Nice.
(Getting hyped up)
Everyone here means business.
They don't want to lose.
It's so neat.
They're so in sync.
Audrey.
(Feeling proud)
Let's go, Audrey.
How are they so in sync?
I love the energy the choreography has.
(Amazed)
A powerful walk.
BADA is a good dancer and a director.
That was great.
(Applause)
(Acknowledging it)
Until the end.
She looks a bit like G-DRAGON.
She sure is cool.
(Tatter, Hyun Se, Jinwoo, YURI, Hee A, Yoon Ji, Envy, Miller)
I could see that she tried to emphasize the concept more...
compared to the mid-point review.
I felt a bit threatened.
- BADA is really... - That's crazy.
But I think INGYOO...
will win.
The impact...
BADA had a better impact,
and INGYOO has better swag.
The judges must have trouble deciding.
Gosh, this is so hard.
Choreographers, please come onto the stage.
INGYOO, let's go!
(Let's go, Team INGYOO!)
(Let's go, Team BADA!)
- BADA! - BADA!
(The cheering battle is becoming competitive.)
I'm very confident.
It was legendary.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
I did everything I could well, and I have no regrets.
The director title...
is mine.
"Directors" is so hard.
It's easy to choose...
- if it isn't "directors." - Exactly.
(Which choreography will win the Director Credit?)
(Sighing)
I really thought hard...
about how to talk about this.
What is it?
I got 100 times more nervous.
I'm feeling a bit nervous.
Watching your performances...
My heart is racing.
My fingers are trembling too.
I thought that both of you directors...
have clearly matured.
It's been so long since I last felt this.
So I want to say, thank you very much.
That's such high praise.
So cool.
First, for INGYOO's performance,
I asked myself,
"Can I perform with that much energy?"
You left such a strong impression.
I'm so envious of the vibe...
which only WE DEM BOYZ can give off.
It was so cool to see you bring out the energy...
befitting of the keyword "madness."
It was very inspiring.
WE DEM BOYZ.
- Who made this. - Let's go!
My team.
The synergy we have isn't something you can overlook.
When that one girl...
came to the front in the middle.
- Here. - I don't know what planet...
you're from, but you're amazing.
That was so cool, the way that was set up.
The movement and the style,
the costumes, the energy.
It felt right.
(It was the right answer.)
Yes!
It was fresh, and it just felt right.
It was a really cool feeling.
The highlight...
had to be Grace.
She performed the way I wanted.
She did it so neatly.
(Very perfect)
I felt very threatened...
and extremely...
competitive.
I want to be evaluated...
by my performance production, not as a dancer.
BADA. You know,
I'm not going to lie. Maybe I'm trying to see...
what you don't do well.
I can't see anything that you do wrong.
I don't know.
Could I ever get such high praise ever again in my life?
You can bring in the sickest dancer in the world,
but if you don't set them up, if you don't reveal them super well,
whether it be music, timing, formations...
But you kind of did it super chill.
Every single person that you wanted to show,
whether it was a friend or a guest...
or just a formation,
every single time somebody came to the front,
it felt like it was chosen.
It felt like it was fresh, and it was presented very well.
It just kept on going. I just want to say congratulations,
and thank you for letting us...
"If I didn't read the synopsis..."
"before watching the performance,"
"would I have recognized it to be a runway?"
That was my biggest worry.
But...
at the end, I thought, "She expressed a runway perfectly."
"She did what she said she would."
I could understand the concept because it was you.
A dancer with a star quality...
who can give off the top model aura.
How many dancers like that do we have in Korea?
It could've been only possible because it was you.
It's up to the director to decide...
which dancer does what to stand out more.
You know what you're best at.
Exactly. That's amazing too.
There's a reason she's so successful.
You being you was the strategy.
It made me...
score you higher.
(Thank you.)
Let's go.
What we did worked.
We scored...
the goal.
This could be more interesting.
Instead of winning by a landslide,
fighting neck and neck...
is more interesting.
I don't lack it.
The confidence.
It's water versus fire.
- Please. - I hope we win.
- Let us know. - We're so desperate.
- Please. - Blue.
I've been never this nervous recently.
I am quite nervous.
Who do you think will win?
- BADA. - You think BADA will win?
I've guessed everything correct so far.
Wouldn't they choose INGYOO?
The 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
Which choreography will showcase their performance to the audience...
and have their name on the credit board?
It will be revealed now.
(BADA versus INGYOO, who is the winner of Last Run?)
(Go, INGYOO!)
Quality of the performance and choreography skills.
I'm confident in them all.
Director BADA?
(Go, BADA!)
Please.
- Please. - Please.
- We did well. - Please.
Whose name will appear?
My heart is about to explode.
I really wanted to take the stage.
I want to win as much as I put in my effort here,
and as much as I spent my time here.
The winner is...
(Nervous)
Please, BADA.
(BADA versus INGYOO, the final result of Last Run)
(To be continued)
(Nervous)
Please, BADA.
(BADA versus INGYOO, the final result of Last Run)
It's BADA!
(BADA has her name on the director's credit.)
(We won.)
(They're completely moved.)
(The moment she saw the result, she sank to the floor.)
Yes!
BADA!
I bawled my eyes out behind my sunglasses.
I thought...
"Am I a decent director?"
It was my goal to succeed as a director.
Did they all vote for INGYOO?
I can't remember what her direction was.
"Is there anything I'm good at?"
It started from the very basic question.
All sorts of thoughts clouded my mind throughout the mission.
The word "Runway" BADA claims...
could be understood by the audience intuitively...
when it's captured on camera, not just us.
That was such a perfect ending.
- For sure. - What the director intended...
was shown very clearly, that she was the designer...
of the stage.
(BADA's runway concept showed her direction very clearly.)
(When she walks toward her team, )
(she gets more emotional.)
(Touched)
"Am I only good as a dancer?"
"Am I a decent director?"
"What should I do to prove myself and be acknowledged?"
(Finally, she was acknowledged as a director.)
They acknowledged the stage that I directed.
"I've led a good life as a director."
"I've lived my life well."
Thanks to that, I got good results.
BADA!
I get to perform happily...
in front of the audience, and I'm grateful for that.
(Bow)
I'm very happy.
(The moment BADA's victory is confirmed, )
(he claps for her.)
Thank you so much.
- Good job. - You were so cool.
(Impressed)
(Both teams did great.)
Good job.
Good job!
(Feeling bad)
I feel bad.
- But we were cool and fiery. - Yes.
It was nice to see you all smile.
Good job!
- Good job! - Good job!
I'm so grateful to them...
for doing their best until the end, treating this like their own stage.
I receive a lot of energy.
(Simeez says sorry to the dancers right after Last Run ends.)
I'm sorry.
- Don't be. - I'm so...
Don't be.
You all prepared so hard.
I felt bad for the dancers who were as passionate as I was.
Saying "we can't perform..."
- is really... - Good job.
I can't face them when I say it.
They believed in me and followed me.
That time was hard for me to bear.
I couldn't bring good results...
(Choking up)
for you, but...
I couldn't produce the result which they could be happy about.
That's the most heartbreaking part.
It'd be nice if we could perform in front of the audience too.
Actually, we're the people who wants to show the audience,
"I'm good, so watch me."
"I made it well, so watch this."
It's a pity that I can't show this to the audience.
We can do this again later.
(Excited)
I really wanted to perform in front of the audience.
The opportunity to showcase my performance as a director.
Honestly, when else would I have the chance?
I should seize the moment.
I still feel shy standing in front of the audience.
Standing in the center as the main dancer...
I still feel rather shy about it.
(Meanwhile, what's happening outside the studio?)
(Countless audience have come to watch the performances.)
The 1st mission by 10 choreographers,
the 1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission.
The results of each round...
have already been decided by Last Run.
The choreographers who have won the match...
can showcase their stages...
in front of you.
I'm envious.
This is so cruel.
Seeing them makes me want to perform.
Renan is the victor.
(Getting chills)
(She catches their eyes with the knee-walking intro.)
This is insane.
It would've been fun if we performed.
The audience would've loved us.
We performed on stage when the losing teams couldn't.
So I was...
I felt amazing.
I'm green with envy. Kim Kasper.
Yes.
I can count on one hand...
the times I performed as the main dancer.
It was a new experience, and I was so grateful.
It's a pity.
We don't want to dance holed up in our rooms.
We want to show it to the audience.
(The newcomer JEONG MIN JUN's stage)
I'm a newcomer.
"Who's this guy?"
They cheered for us so loudly.
I can feel the energy on the stage.
I was so grateful.
I've looked forward to this moment.
I wanted to show them who BABYZOO is...
and what kind of dance he does.
(BADA's performance brings it to a grand close.)
(Overwhelmed)
(Screaming)
(It's so cool!)
It is explosive.
(A very smart and impactful part, making full use of the dancers)
I love this part.
(The latter part of the performance is very explosive.)
She's so good.
I felt a lot of regret.
My performance would've brought upon louder cheers.
The audience saw the stage that I directed...
and cheered and supported it.
It was a dream come true.
I'm so honored to have been able to perform.
I was grateful.
I'll soon take the director title.
I'll keep going. The mega crew mission was so fierce.
Please!
What is it now?
What on earth is that?
What is it?
Gosh, hold on.
What's that?
What's this?
This... Hold on, NaiN.
We're the mannequins this time.
This is crazy.
There were exactly ten.
I saw the mannequins with our names.
A dancer?
Wait, a dancer?
Wait.
It says "choreographer" in front.
(It's written "choreographer" in front of the bib.)
Hold on.
You're right. The back says "dancer" and the front says "choreographer."
It said "dancer" behind...
and "choreographer" in front.
You can rip it.
You're right. Does it mean we could become...
either a dancer or a choreographer?
The name tags were made of Velcro so you could remove them.
Anyway, the roles will be split up among the ten of us.
Who will become the director?
And who will become just dancers?
This is the directors' version of Class Mission.
I'm scared.
Among us?
These directors will become dancers?
I want to become the director, of course.
They're top talents.
When else would I be able to direct them?
I must become the director.
As someone who directs others,
I don't think I can stand being directed.
It's been way too long since I was directed.
If I can't become a director, I need to go home.
I'm not exactly early in my career.
It'll hurt my pride if I become a dancer.
I should become a director.
- A director. - I must become a director.
I don't just want to dance.
It's not a dancers' survival show.
I must do my best as a director.
This is a directors' survival show, after all.
To get your name on the Director Credit,
you must prove your worth once again.
The second mission of...
Street World Fighter: Directors' War.
How will they choose a director?
It's completely veiled.
It is...
the Title Sequence Film Mission.
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
What is it?
What?
Isn't this the film they play when the show starts?
The one minute given to make an impression of the show.
It captures the identity of the show.
This mission will evaluate your sense...
as a film director.
That's good. I like making films.
I've worked on it a few times.
I was confident.
Anything is possible with a film.
I'm a bit better at it, and I like it too.
What you think about...
Street World Fighter: Directors' War.
Its universe, the choreographers' characters,
the film's tone and framing,
and your sense as a director.
You must capture all of these in one video.
That's the difficult part.
How will you capture the charm of these ten choreographers...
and convey it directly?
Those who watch the show...
The ones who watch the show are the viewers.
No matter who watches,
I wan them to be able to say, "That was incredible."
The intention of the opening.
I think that has to be expressed well.
Who will make the face of this show?
- Gosh. - Gosh.
The ten choreographers...
will create film draft videos.
We'll be filming the title draft.
Through those draft videos,
the director who will lead the Title Sequence Film Mission...
will be decided.
Thus, this mission...
will consist of just one director...
and nine choreographers...
who will work under that director.
Who will become the dancers?
Me? It can never be me.
I'm here for a director battle.
I must become the director.
I'm certain I will come up with something better.
For the production of the film draft videos,
you will work with the draft dancers.
The draft dancers...
will replace all ten choreographers including yourself.
Gosh, this is a headache.
Where and how will I find replacements for these people?
We had to cast dancers for each role.
They'll be the draft dancers...
who will be dancing in our place.
We need the ones who can match...
the lines of the choreographers...
along with their styles.
I started writing names as soon as I arrived.
The one who will take Koo Young's role.
The one who will take INGYOO's role.
You must prove through the video...
why you must become the director.
Just like the Class Mission, we must make the others...
- want to do it. - Right. That's what we have to do.
"Will I become the director, dancer, or choreographer?"
It's a mission that will determine that.
The title song will be revealed.
- What? - There's a song?
There's a song for this.
("Royalty" produced by Illmind, Yoon Mi Rae, Tiger JK)
- "Royalty." - "Royalty."
Oh!
It was a style that I liked.
"It's so good!"
It's so good. I think I can do a good job with it.
It's Yoon Mi Rae.
I'm someone who can work with any genre.
It feels like a match for me.
MIN JUN and Hash looked quite worried.
They weren't people who made drafts.
That's not true.
It was a song in a style I wanted,
so I felt relieved.
I thought I could make something nice with it.
I got a visual idea of what it would look like.
Once this mission ends,
for the first time,
two choreographers will get eliminated.
Oh, my gosh!
I got so surprised.
Wasn't it one person?
Two?
We're getting eliminated already?
Ten people did feel like a lot.
Eight was a better number.
Let's make it four.
Maybe five?
The final battle of survival...
that will decide the first ones to get eliminated.
It's the Last Stage.
- There are so many "lasts." - Gosh!
No more "lasts!"
Last Stage is an improvised directing battle...
in which the contestants must prove their worth one last time.
- This is going to be interesting. - This is going to be interesting.
The conditions of this Last Stage...
are 24 hours...
and a table and chair.
I feel dizzy all of a sudden.
That made no sense at all.
It stressed me out. It was going to make my hair fall out.
Within 24 hours,
you must create your own work...
including the table and chair.
I'm about to go crazy.
(Sighing)
On top of that,
the one who becomes the director of this mission...
will be exempted from elimination.
The director will also be given...
the right to decide on the elimination candidates...
as a Judge.
Gosh! I didn't expect that at all.
I must win that position.
Really? Gosh.
The director becomes the Judge.
That was an unbelievable benefit.
I got so surprised. The director becomes the Judge.
It felt so cruel.
After becoming the director,
being able to enter the safe zone is a big benefit in itself.
They did well to make everyone want that position.
It's an actual war.
I will make sure to put up my name as the director.
Thus, beyond securing survival,
the director will be in a position to be able to...
decide on the fates of the other choreographers.
One of us will take the throne...
and handle the others like slaves.
The Title Sequence Film Mission...
isn't just about coming up with the title of the show.
Only one director will be chosen...
and the elimination candidates who will head to the Last Stage...
will be decided through this mission.
That's a huge right.
It's a position that everyone would want.
I believe the director can choose...
who to eliminate.
I must win.
It's because I must become the champion.
That can never happen.
I will survive until the end.
In Directors' War,
isn't that the biggest authority?
Right away?
This is a casting war.
Finding dancers is the problem.
I must get to them first before the others.
Should I call them now?
I must call the dancers.
I have to find dancers who can take our roles.
Isn't this insane?
I'm going to lose my hair.
Are you going to get me a hair transplant?
The dancers have to suit all ten of our characters.
I must make the choreographers want to perform my work.
I must film a draft that can bring out...
each choreographer's qualities...
to be able to get a lot of votes and become the director.
It's hard to find the dancers.
Gosh, I think Tae Woo will call Nino.
(Peeking at Kasper's room)
Who should I call?
I had to call the dancers I wanted first.
Nino will take INGYOO's role.
Nino has a sense of arrogance to him.
I thought he was a perfect match as a character.
I thought Nino was suitable for that role.
If he doesn't work with me,
it's pure betrayal.
Shuri will take BADA's role.
(He calls Shuri right away.)
Hey, Shuri.
I called to cast you.
Shuri for Kasper's role.
Shuri!
Shuri will definitely ask Kasper.
(Kasper's role: Shuri)
Shuri for Kasper's role.
I think everyone will think the same.
I must move quickly.
The only one who can cover his skills and damping...
is Shuri in my opinion.
I contacted Shuri.
(Shuri! Can you join me for a draft mission on June 2?)
I didn't get back from him yet.
Why are you all gathered together?
Koo Young's role is the hardest.
(Peeking)
(Gazing)
You look busy. Who contacted you?
No.
Shuri contacted me.
What?
No way.
He told me that BADA contacted him.
(Screaming)
(Escaping reality)
That got me flustered quite a lot.
This punk read my message and didn't reply.
That was why I texted him again.
"Why aren't you answering me? Please join me."
Shuri will come to me this time.
He is only human.
(Shuri was cast by 4 choreographers.)
This is a battle for Shuri.
Shuri is my child.
I can never get him taken away from me.
Without thinking about the consequences,
I'm going to go for the best way possible.
I'm confident when it comes to films.
I'm 100 percent certain about this.
The others are here to prove themselves.
I must be able to prove myself as well.
The title of director is mine.
(D-Day of Title Sequence Film Mission draft shoot)
Thank you.
(The 10 directors and dancers have gathered for the draft shoot.)
Thank you so much for helping out with the draft.
Each of you will become the director...
for this draft.
Many of our dancers have gathered...
to help me out.
The dancers are really important during the draft shoot.
I felt this while being a director.
Choreographies get chosen...
based on the draft dancers.
That's how important they are.
But I hit a red light based on that.
BADA! Shuri will take BADA's role.
(Team Kasper: BADA's role, Shuri)
He's like a son to me.
He's always assisting me.
Kasper!
(She didn't get a reply from him yesterday.)
Shuri!
(Team BADA: Kasper's role, Shuri)
You're the only one who can take this role.
But with Shuri...
That's impossible.
Even if he wants to help out with all of us,
it's right for us to avoid using him.
I'll step away from the battle for Shuri.
Hoi will take Kasper's role.
(In sync with Kasper 100 percent?)
And Kasper.
Kasper is my key ring guy.
He will become the key ring guy of the key ring guy.
He's working hard.
And INGYOO's role...
(Team BABYZOO: INGYOO's role)
will be taken by Lee Jung!
(Fully acceptable)
It's because...
(INJUNG's "like JENNIE")
Lee Jung has been friends with INGYOO for a decade.
Yes, right.
She understands INGYOO's characteristics so well.
- Exactly! - Right.
INGYOO.
(Team Back Koo Young: INGYOO's role, no: ze)
Okay!
You've grown much taller, INGYOO.
(Laughing)
She's incredible with these drafts.
And here's Ms. Lia Kim.
- Hash! - Right.
- I did my hair just like hers. - Right.
- The side-swept bangs. - Right.
Hash is really flexible.
She can pull off all kinds of techniques.
Right! These moves!
- These moves! - "I got it!"
We must dance like the ones we're given?
- Well... - While imagining that person?
Don't dance like them.
Say this to BADA, "You want to do this, don't you?"
This is a better approach.
It's like, "You want to do this, don't you, Koo Young?"
(Vata is confused.)
It's the draft of the Title Sequence Film Mission.
What's being seen now is a completely rough draft.
I'm quite detailed when filming for drafts.
Are the lights different in color on purpose?
- We're working on them. - Okay.
This is the only mood light.
Is this the spotlight?
- It's the spotlight. - Okay.
As soon as the spotlight turned on, the blue light disappears.
This one.
I think this is the right tone for the blue one.
The key point of the Title Sequence.
The lights.
There's a certain mood that can be felt from the lights.
Something only the lights can express.
Only the lights are expressed in the video...
and only the lights can lighten up the stage.
The dancers under those lights.
"How will the mood feel with the lights?"
The lights control the mood.
- Hey. - Yes?
Come here, Ye Hwan.
Ye Hwan has Koo Young's role.
You will be given a very important mission.
You're part of the lighting crew now.
Here. Like this.
This is really important.
At this pace?
Right. Boom!
The cameraman will come.
At that moment...
Flash!
Flash the light constantly like this.
Okay!
(Take 1, 1st attempt)
Nice!
(In the zone)
You shouldn't shine it downward, Ye Hwan.
The light has to lighten up everything.
(Take 2, lighting the whole room)
Don't feel the rhythm too much.
Move it around gently.
(Take 3, moving slowly)
You have to move from here to here.
(Lighting it slowly toward the front)
(The cameraman is satisfied.)
We did it!
(The key ring guy of the light lover is found.)
The biggest focus is on me becoming the director.
I must get that title.
It's a problem if I lose to them, isn't it?
A punk like Kasper... No.
Gosh!
Guys like them will give me directions.
"Hey, move back more to the left!"
That is what will happen to me.
If that happens, I must head back to my hometown.
Yes!
During the Signature 400 Mission,
I wasn't able to get my name on the Credit Board.
With this mission,
the director's name will appear during every episode.
I must show everyone who I am.
I want to become the director.
Please help me become the director!
I'm satisfied with the draft.
The one-minute video that will represent this show.
I felt confident.
Great! I love this place.
Let's go!
(Showroom)
(The place responsible for the casual looks of the directors)
Should we enter the showroom?
- Yes! - Yes!
We're wearing their pants.
Right. The pants.
Black and gray!
(Today's OOTD: Black and gray)
I really wanted those.
- The black ones? - The black ones look nice.
It's such a nice fit.
I really wanted this.
The color that suits cool tones.
- Yes! - Nice!
- How's the color? - It looks nice.
It looks nice, doesn't it? I want it!
(BABYZOO's pick is the stylish gray windbreaker.)
Are the colors the same, NaiN?
Your setup is insane right now.
This really looks nice.
It looks really nice when I wear it.
"It looks really nice when I wear it."
- Gosh! - What kind of comment is that?
A vivid color like this suits MIN JUN.
Right.
(He gets excited after hearing his compliment.)
(I feel great.)
- Gray! - Gray!
(They get ready to work...)
(after brightening up their moods with some shopping.)
Let's see how everyone does.
I'm expecting great qualities from everyone.
It's making me feel nervous.
Gosh! I feel quite satisfied.
After putting together the video yesterday,
I thought that I should be the one to become director.
Oh, gosh!
(A video is played in all rooms of the directors.)
(What's this?)
I will now explain how the director will get chosen...
for the Title Sequence Film Mission.
How the director will get chosen.
I was curious about this.
Hold on! We have to watch this together.
Why am I watching this on my own.
The ten choreographers will first reveal...
the film draft videos they worked on.
Before revealing the video,
each choreographer must explain the key points...
of the visuals, story, and characters.
The directions of the video must be explained.
Gosh, we have to make a presentation?
Once the film draft videos get revealed,
through an evaluation of the choreographers...
two director candidates will get decided.
The 2 director candidates will use 9 dancers...
to complete the final draft video.
The director candidates...
will participate in each other's videos.
(What?)
(Freezing)
So we should do it twice?
The draft videos...
must be performed by the actual choreographers...
under two directors?
It's going to be so hard if I don't become the director.
Sharing things is inevitable in this situation.
It's a matter of who doesn't get shaken and maintains their style.
Is there another way to decide...
the final director out of the two?
The final director of the Title Sequence Film Mission...
will be decided by the final draft videos...
made by the two director candidates.
The votes of eight choreographers...
excluding the two director candidates...
and one vote of the Public Judge will decide the final director.
The other eight choreographers...
will evaluate the directing skills...
of the two director candidates.
I must become a candidate.
Pick me!
I hope I become one of the two candidates.
As a result, the one candidate with the most votes...
will become the director of the Title Sequence Film...
of Street World Fighter: Directors' War.
The final director...
will also be given the right of the Judge...
to decide on the candidates for the Last Stage.
(Screaming)
That's so scary!
I really hope it isn't me.
Gosh, that's quite scary. I don't like that.
I will be in danger if I don't become the director.
That made me feel scared.
Even after become a director candidate,
that person can also end up being on the Last Stage...
if they fail to become the final director.
Gosh! Someone will feel a lot of stress.
Out of the ten choreographers,
who will become the director...
to complete the first scene...
of Street World Fighter: Directors' War?
Me! I hope it's me.
It will definitely be me...
and Back Koo Young.
Even after hearing that there were going to be two director candidates,
I felt confident.
It won't make sense if mine doesn't get picked.
I'm really confident.
I put together a video...
that will make the others want to perform it.
I'm confident.
(Concept and film draft video reveal)
(The concept and video reveal begins.)
Oh, no!
I'm scared!
(Concept and film draft video reveal)
Hello. I'm the first one up. I'm BABYZOO.
(Excited)
I'm so curious.
BABYZOO worked really hard.
The Title Sequence Film...
is the first video that gets revealed to the public.
The one-minute video that will represent this show.
The ones who watch the show...
are the viewers.
Mass appeal can't be ignored.
As it's that kind of video,
I slightly made a light approach.
You will notice when you watch the draft video.
The intro had "Countdown."
"Countdown?"
I worked on a pose before the start of a race.
The stopwatch is pressed to announce our start.
We did hand signs with each other to represent a good competition.
There are 5 men and 5 women.
I thought a pair move was necessary.
(The pair part is quite hot.)
I believed the public would like that part.
Then, what exactly is the concept?
Is it a race or...
I think the concept...
is that we're starting a competition together.
There wasn't a specific concept.
It was a piece that was focused toward the public.
I think the public...
The public will be...
The public...
It exceeds the quality I expected.
I'm sure the public will love it.
I'm confident.
- Are we watching it now? - I'm excited.
I'm excited!
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(Choreography Concept Credit Board, BABYZOO)
I like the "Countdown" part.
It's Renan!
Lee Jung took INGYOO's role?
Why do I look so excited?
It's fancy.
Gosh, that's amazing.
That's impressive!
Yes! Kasper!
Hey!
It's really nice.
Hyun Se is playing my role?
This part suits BADA.
It's dancing from start to finish.
They're dancing in pairs!
This looks nice.
I also like this part.
(You can watch BABYZOO's full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
- Nice! - Nice!
That was exciting.
This move looks cool.
I would've never thought of that.
(I'll bite my top as well.)
Gosh, that was nice. He did well with the choreography.
I loved the biting part.
The flow of the choreography was really nice.
It looked so exciting that I wanted to learn it.
Many people said the choreography was nice.
(Chuckling)
Yes!
To be honest, it felt great.
It was really nice.
But one thing that was disappointing...
What?
Was the pair part.
(The pair part of 5 men and 5 women)
It was a good idea as there were men and women.
But this is what gets me.
"We have to watch pair parts every episode?"
The theme of theTitle Sequence Film Mission...
was to represent our show and the ten choreographers.
A pair part all of a sudden?
Twerking was done out of nowhere.
There are many pair moves out there,
but in afro dancing,
there should be something sensual.
It was funny to see MIN JUN and Hash as a pair.
In the video, MIN JUN gestured pulling...
Hash's hips up and down.
I found that funny.
(MIN JUN, Hash)
In the choreography, I had to bounce my hips up and down.
Then MIN JUN had to pretend to pull.
That was quite shocking.
I found it funny that I had to do the same with NaiN.
(INGYOO and NaiN are twerking side by side.)
So watching your choreography made me wonder...
if the direction matched...
the level of directors here.
(Surprised by his blunt comment)
I just didn't get it.
Why were...
female directors suddenly twerking?
He failed to capture the gravitas...
of the directors.
The pair dance?
I'm certain of this.
If the viewers watch my video,
they'll go, "I'd love to see them dance this version."
I'm sure of it.
I was a bit disappointed.
Would it be okay...
if you didn't read the paper now?
(The concept paper was handed out in advance.)
Could I go over the presentation slides first?
Presentation slides?
We're on a tight schedule. When on earth...
did she put together the slides?
I can only imagine just how much work she put into this.
This is the Title Sequence Film Mission.
I'm sure everyone did...
a great job with the video.
First of all, for this Film Mission,
I believe that the concept matters the most.
With that in mind, I decided on...
"The Matrix."
When I heard that she chose "The Matrix" for her concept,
I thought it was original and sounded fun.
She's a genius when it comes to crafting concepts.
I really wanted to steal her concept.
Deciding on the narrative took more time...
than coming up with the choreography.
It's perfect.
I decided to go with "The Matrix" as my concept.
This is it.
It suits my choreography style.
And it's going to look amazing.
It's just the perfect choice across the board.
When I thought of the movie, a few colors came to mind.
Metal, black, and green.
Those are my key colors.
This is my mood board.
I feel very confident when it comes to styling.
I agree. Yes.
Her styling for "Avatar" was great.
It was incredible.
Simeez's presentation was...
by far the best.
"This is the vibe."
"This is the mood board."
"Here are the key points."
She prepared her presentation to persuade us.
My gosh. I really thought...
she was going to win this.
I was determined to become the director for this mission.
Let's watch my choreography video now.
I was expecting something amazing.
I can't wait.
(Choreography Concept Credit Board Simeez)
Emma is in the video.
She went with five girls.
She did a good job bringing out my dance style.
I can pull that off, right?
You have to keep dancing.
Right. I have to keep dancing.
Some parts of the choreograph fell short.
She hasn't grasped my style as a dancer.
A few of those moves came across twerking.
I was a bit worried about that.
I didn't see much dancing on the staircase.
The choreography felt a bit hollow.
I'm always on my knees.
(Feeling guilty, laughing)
I guess that's in every choreography.
That must be MIN JUN's thing.
It looked unique and fun.
Why did Simeez dance for my part?
It was the first time...
I've ever seen Simeez take on a male part.
That change was quite refreshing. I liked it.
(You can watch Simeez's full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
As soon as I watched the video,
I felt that her choreography didn't quite live up...
to her presentation.
It made me wonder why she chose "The Matrix."
It was disappointing...
that the choreography didn't connect to the concept.
The choreography had nothing to do...
with the concept.
When I was listening to her presentation,
I thought her pitch was really cool...
and she was super professional.
I thought it was going to be great.
But when I watched the video,
I was like, "What? What's this?"
They didn't seem to match.
Where's the connection to "The Matrix?"
Which part of the routine is supposed to fit the concept?
I kept getting these questions in my head.
Only after watching my first draft,
she commented that she didn't see how "The Matrix" fit in.
This shows how limited her view is.
Which part are you exactly referring to?
I don't get it.
If your choreography...
fit the concept better...
and was more convincing enough...
But...
this video is only a draft.
Telling me that you didn't capture the concept enough...
only after watching this is a bit too much...
in my opinion.
I was quite flustered.
Why?
At the end of the day, the video...
has to be enough to express the concept.
But if the video can't do that,
it means she failed, doesn't it?
This is my personal opinion. This was supposed to be a film.
When filming the choreography video as a draft for a K-pop artist,
I'm not a fan...
of using a wide-angle lens...
to direct the front-and-back movements.
The atmosphere felt ice-cold.
What is this?
It was a film, so I expected to see cinematic directions.
They just moved around the gimbal.
There were a few camera transitions.
Her video pretty much followed...
the typical format of K-pop choreography videos.
I can go on and on about K-pop...
since that's the industry I work in.
But...
it sounded like he was looking down on K-pop.
I just don't get it.
"How could he look down on it?"
"And he's young too."
(He's young too.)
Kasper,
please give out your concept paper.
(INGYOO checks the concept paper.)
(Gasping)
(Shocked)
What's this?
What is it?
My goodness. What's this?
No way.
- "The Matrix." - My goodness.
- It's the same concept. - This is fun.
My concept is super strong.
I don't think my concept...
- will overlap with anyone's. - It's perfect.
(During her concept presentation)
("The Matrix")
(He saw that she chose the same concept as him.)
"My gosh. Look at her."
"We're not so different." That's what I thought.
Coincidentally, Hee Jung and I...
chose the same concept for this mission.
But our interpretation is different.
So keep that in mind.
He took the opposite direction...
to capture this concept, "The Matrix."
Simeez worked really hard to visualize the concept...
and incorporate it into his choreography.
When taking on this mission,
I wanted to maximize everyone's character.
In my piece,
INGYOO is...
the main character.
(Me?)
(Why INGYOO, all of a sudden?)
Kasper isn't sought-after as a choreography in the industry.
It's like...
he's buying a new product at an outlet.
The bad blood between INGYOO and Kasper is real.
He's the main character.
It felt nice.
So INGYOO...
will be portraying the system error in the choreography.
(A system error)
A system error.
You are one in real life too.
I liked that it captured my position on this show.
I'm like a glitch on this show.
I do some things on this show that make me look like a glitch.
INGYOO has the bad boy position on the show.
Everyone would agree with this concept.
This kind of idea is fun.
He's going to be the system error.
I did my best to portray his arrogance...
in the video.
(Choreography Concept Credit Board)
(It's not on pause.)
What's going on? What is it?
The entire intro was just blank.
I think the intro plays a crucial role.
Those ten seconds are so precious.
That was the most disappointing part.
The choreography had...
unique movements.
I couldn't stop watching.
I guess that's me.
He even utilized the lighting.
That does look fun.
Koo Young and MIN JUN.
I thought it'd be fun to do that with Simeez.
(The 2nd system error)
He picked a good color for the lighting that fit the mood.
Setting the mood is all about the lighting.
- Who's that? - It's BABYZOO.
(It's BABYZOO's part.)
(The 3rd system error)
He skipped adding any moves here.
But that's pretty cool.
He went with such bold decisions.
I liked the move for the breathing part.
(The system error is satisfied with it.)
The choreography for the chorus is amazing.
It's good, isn't it?
(It goes like this.)
I wanted to steal the choreography for the chorus.
It was super catchy.
I liked your bold decision...
to keep the choreography for the chorus simple.
I thought assigning me the system error as my role...
could be a secret weapon...
compared to the other draft we saw earlier.
Your use of lighting...
made the concept click for the audience.
When you think of the movie,
you'd think of the red pill and the blue pill.
Integrating that as the main theme...
made sense in terms of props.
This is so disappointing.
It'd be crazy if mine doesn't get chosen.
I'm super confident.
I have a question.
When transitioning into the group choreography,
everyone stays still.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three...
He has to build up the momentum all over again.
If he wants that to be the highlight,
the formation has to go from messy to neat.
I think that approach is more appropriate for this.
But it wasn't.
I'm most curious why you didn't go with the opposite flow.
I didn't get it.
MIN JUN and I...
just focus on different things.
Our views are different.
First of all...
The thing is that,
I come with choreography that they want to dance.
- The chorus choreography is great. - It is, isn't it?
That was my priority.
But...
he asked me this ridiculous question.
I had the most difficult time understanding that.
This is the Title Sequence Film Mission.
The artistic quality of the video looked a bit iffy.
What about yours then?
MIN JUN has strong opinions...
and a strong personality.
He has a lot of ideas he wants to express.
He was...
just...
attacking my choreography.
I'm a bit flustered.
MIN JUN.
Let's check yours out then.
(The fourth choreographer to present the concept and video)
(JEONG MIN JUN)
I'm up against nine choreographers in this mission.
There's this pressure...
that I should be the director and put out a great piece.
I have to stand out.
As soon as I heard the song,
the movie, "The Thieves," came to mind.
And the bomb scene orchestrated by the Joker...
in "The Dark Knight" came to mind too.
Let's see if yours looks like a film.
Let's see how good you are.
It's called the Title Sequence Film Mission.
It will be the title sequence of the show.
Taking a cinematic approach would give me an edge.
The directors show up in a car.
Then they share the blueprint and the plan.
As BADA gets out of the car,
she puts on a timer on the car.
But that's a timer for the dynamite.
I'm looking forward to watch his video.
I'm curious as to how he'll play this out.
Toward the end of the story, we see the bomb on the car.
Just when the ten of us are about to throw something...
at the building in the back,
the building is going to explode.
That's the kind of direction I'm hoping to stage.
I think his goal was...
to give a very cinematic touch to his video.
It will be fun to film this.
I knew it. MIN JUN is the king of storylines.
This is why I lost to him.
If I'm not the director in this mission,
I'll just be a dancer.
I wanted to be the director.
I can't wait to watch it.
I had high expectations.
Honestly, I didn't expect much from him.
I don't think I'll like it, but I was curious.
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(Choreography Concept Credit Board)
(The choreographers show up in a car.)
(BADA gets out of the car.)
It's Piki.
(She puts the timer for the dynamite on the car.)
(The choreographers enter the building.)
(They carry out their own tasks.)
He focused more on the cinematic aspect,
- not the choreography. - Yes. Totally.
The storyline he had in mind didn't come through in the video.
It would've been neater...
if we didn't see them bringing the mirror.
The transitions weren't my style.
That's supposed to be a running scene, right?
Which part of this film is supposed to...
remind us of "The Thieves?"
I didn't see the motif in the video.
Given the lengthy explanation he gave us,
his video lacked substance. It was disappointing.
I got the feeling that it was very one-dimensional.
I only remember seeing the dance.
(The 10 choreographers blow up the building.)
Personally, I was disappointed.
I watched it while picturing it as the title sequence.
The problem was that...
it sort of turned out half-baked.
Contrary to what you promised us, the video wasn't...
convincing enough for your idea to come through.
Gosh, he's so scary.
You gave us a lengthy presentation.
You used the car for the countdown.
At the end, we throw something,
and the bomb explodes. So the building blows up.
I don't quite understand how the middle part fits in here.
This is the title sequence?
The more I thought about it, the less it worked in my head.
He made it sound like he planned a lot for it,
but it didn't come through.
"I've been thinking a lot about it for as long as I can remember."
"I gave it a lot of thought."
"I had to go abroad and even make a transfer."
"Once I landed, it took me a three-hour ride to get there."
"Then I went through all sorts of trouble to find this."
"Afterward, I brought it back to Korea with utmost care."
"This is the instant rice."
That's how it felt.
What he promised us and the video didn't match.
That must've been why.
After watching his video, it was obvious that...
he had limited experience in working with other teams.
Can I be brutally honest?
It looked like a midterm project from a college student.
(I see.)
My college assignments...
used to look exactly like that.
The story itself was substantial.
But he just ended up filming in different places.
If this were a college assignment, I would've given him an A plus.
But this is Street World Fighter: Directors' War.
For that to be the title sequence,
his film failed to convey the identity of the show.
Anyone who can understand my intention would instantly get it.
But a lot of them didn't get it.
So that was frustrating.
I don't think you did a good job...
of bringing each dancer's character to life.
The lyrics went, "Nod your head."
So that's what he did, and I hated it.
(Nod your head)
I hate one-dimensional approaches.
As for my part,
you included the type of move I liked the least.
Even before doing this mission, this was the type of role...
I considered the worst for me.
I did a few turns and did a jump.
It was shocking.
I'm not a dancer who can just do turns and jumps.
(Shocked)
That was quite disappointing.
MIN JUN failed to understand her style.
- Right. - Yes.
Thank you.
(Surprised)
(Shocked)
I was quite surprised.
It caught me off guard.
(The choreographers are flustered after seeing her concept paper.)
I was fascinated.
Let me go over my concept first.
My concept is The Heist.
BADA had the same concept as me.
(His concept was "The Thieves.")
I'm doomed.
(BADA chose the same concept as MIN JUN which is "The Thieves.")
It was shocking.
- We're thieves. - Gosh. This is crazy.
So those two picked "The Thieves" for their concept.
I was really shocked because MIN JUN and I chose...
the same concept.
As soon as I saw his concept,
my mind went blank. I thought, "I'm doomed."
It's the same concept.
I thought I was the only one who came up with this idea.
"No!"
"Oh, no. This is mine."
I thought about ways to make my presentation stand out.
So I was going to make sure my concept came through.
I thought our show was about keeping what's yours...
while trying to steal someone else's.
I wanted to make good use of the props.
This treasure box is the main visual element and key point.
I'm going to build the routine...
from the staging to choreography around this treasure box.
I wanted my choreography to stand out.
This is the move when the song goes, "royalty."
(BADA's signature dance move)
So something like this.
(The catchy dance move...)
(makes them try it out right away.)
Oh, my neck.
It was nice. But to be honest,
the concept is too plain.
Everyone's done the heist concept before.
(BADA and MIN JUN's concept: "The Thieves")
I can't even count...
how many performances I created around the heist concept. I mean it.
THE BOYZ released a song called...
"The Stealer."
(THE BOYZ's song, "The Stealer")
They performed the song at nine different awards ceremonies.
I came up with 9 performances in 2 months with the same concept.
The setups were all different.
I've done all kinds of things with this concept. Seriously.
(The master of the heist concept, Back Koo Young)
Personally, I'm sick of this heist concept.
If they're going to use this concept for the title sequence film,
it has to be a lot more elaborate. If they can pull this off,
I would be able to treat it as a title sequence film.
It was the same concept as mine.
I was curious to see...
how her interpretation differed from mine.
(BADA's video is revealed.)
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(Choreography Concept Credit Board)
(The master of the heist concept is looking forward to it.)
Oh, yes.
That's the role Shuri took.
Wait. Shuri?
This is a total betrayal, plain and simple.
She gave meaning to every single scene.
That was disappointing.
I saw a lot of moves...
I knew I could pull off well.
I thought her film was closer...
to matching the heist concept between the two.
I thought her choreography was neat and tight.
I liked it.
I liked her signature move.
(Getting hooked...)
(the second they see it)
I like this part.
The composition highlighted...
the lead choreographer and the secondary choreographer.
This will be the first video of the show.
This is going to be the face of the show in a way.
My focus in this mission was elevating the staging...
and cinematic quality...
while taking the choreography to the next level.
This clip won't show up in the middle of the competition.
It will be the title sequence. Considering that element,
MIN JUN's version was a bit light. So that was disappointing.
As for BADA's version, they had the same concept.
Looking at her choreography and setups,
I liked how some of her moves...
that really grounded the performance.
I saw some moves I knew I could deliver well.
(What did the master of the heist concept think?)
What's the point of telling you my opinion about BADA?
She's so good.
This heist concept is speaking to me now.
I liked that you continued using the prop until the end...
to keep the identity going.
If I were to assume that a trophy was in the treasure box,
utilizing it for the Title Sequence Film Mission...
would fit the objective. It worked well with the film.
It must be a direct result of her cinematic insight,
her understanding of this mission,
and her years of experience on large-scale projects.
It could very well be me.
It seemed like there was a glimmer of hope.
It makes me want to keep making...
the signature dance move.
I keep doing "Royalty."
- So... - What?
(Royalty)
This signature move is...
delicious.
Yummy. Is it because BADA did it?
Getting INGYOO to say something is delicious is truly like...
plucking a star from the sky.
I was really happy when he said the choreography...
for the chorus was delicious.
The downside is that each dancer has an assigned character.
(BADA assigned a specific character to each choreographer.)
It was difficult to capture the essence of the character...
and convey the intended meaning...
within such a brief scene.
In the first section,
only the treasure chest is visible, rather than people.
Trying to capture our dancing in such a short time,
it might actually get in the way.
It might feel a bit disappointing...
since the focus is on the treasure chest...
rather than people.
Leave the worrying about the props to me.
Give it to me as homework.
I think they'll pin a little hope on me.
Hash. Please come out.
(Presenting concept and draft video, the sixth choreographer Hash)
(Winking)
(Smiling)
Hash and I mostly competed against each other.
I have never directed...
a music video on my own.
But I was certain I possessed that sense.
Since this film serves to properly introduce...
the ten individuals...
in Street World Fighter: Director's War,
I wanted to craft a strong storyline.
I decided to let the atmosphere drive the narrative.
It's nice and simple.
It was similar to what I thought.
I appreciated her honesty in saying she wanted to keep it simple.
I think she did well.
(Agreeing)
(Choreography Concept Credit Board, Hash)
- This is going to be fun. - Yes.
It's cool.
The person playing me is really cool.
Simeez.
Cute.
Hash isn't Hash.
That's nice.
It was really innovative.
The choreography was very professional.
The variety of camera angles and fields of view was great.
This time you kneeled.
Right.
I wanted to see the chorus choreography,
but the screen suddenly split into three, so I couldn't see it.
It disrupted my concentration.
She's like Renan.
I thought it was Renan.
(Clapping)
(Satisfied)
The strength is the transition utilizing the glasses.
The eyeglass frame.
I liked the eyeglass frame because it was so fresh.
I thought the idea of having the dancers lying down...
be dragged away to express the music was a creative choice...
in terms of camera angles.
The shot where Renan is left behind...
looks a bit cute, but I wonder...
if it really matches her current image.
This video will be used for the opening.
Among all the videos I've seen so far,
it showcased the most diverse range of people within a minute.
You also put a lot of thought into how to utilize...
the dancers for each character.
It shows that you've really studied the character.
I was grateful that he recognized that.
But,
the tempo was too fast.
I understand because it was only a minute.
NaiN, Renan,
MIN JUN, then Hash...
(Non-stop switching between dancers)
It's fast.
If there had been even just a clear moment of rest,
it would have provided some breathing room and relief.
I don't know.
I can see that you've done...
a lot of analysis to bring the character to life.
But the background choreography...
was too "Hash-style."
What's wrong with "Hash-style?"
I was a bit frustrated.
The video we shot...
will continue to be played as the title sequence.
Taking that into account,
if the directors have a good sense for these things,
they'll choose mine.
Here we go.
I kept reminding myself that it was the opening video for the show.
So I wanted to properly shine a spotlight...
on each choreographer's character.
INGYOO and I thought exactly the same way.
(At the time of the concept presentation)
(They wanted to bring out the character of each choreographer.)
So that each person leaves a lasting impression to some extent.
I make a living by assigning parts.
I kept him somewhat in check.
Shall we look at the concept image? I have a few images.
I have improvised a setup inside the closed-down mart.
Hash is going to dance here.
(Me?)
"What?" I was taken aback.
Hash will show...
technique and character.
She'll run inside...
and people will catch her inside the tent.
He created a solo part by utilizing me.
It had a glamorous feel.
I was looking forward to it.
Next, it transitions to MIN JUN.
I'll use the space...
with the stairs for the first verse.
I'm looking forward to it.
I like that I have a role to play.
BADA will...
Simeez...
In case of Koo Young...
Do it in one take if possible...
It felt like each person was being shown...
and introduced..
In sync with the title sequence.
Perhaps it might help showcase my strengths...
in the first video.
Honestly, I was really tempted.
This is a draft for the Title Sequence Film Mission.
I am confident I can pull this off beautifully.
I think they'll be persuaded.
Just take a look.
Seeing is believing.
I'm really looking forward to it.
(Choreography Concept Credit Board, INGYOO)
The intro was really cool.
He gave her a solo part.
Hash.
If the parts are handled individually,
it can come across as loose to the viewer.
He used various staging elements for the solo part.
It was great.
What? It's Vata.
WE DEM BOYZ's distinct style...
really shone through.
It's the style I like.
The camera movement was really simple.
You absolutely have to use "get down on your knees."
- Me. - What? Look at that.
(Laughing)
It had a tribal vibe.
Impactful choreography.
Kamel is so good.
The choreography is good.
I don't think I can dance like Kamel.
Mood Dog is here too.
(Silence after the video)
Regarding the theme of Title Sequence Film Mission...
Is this a film...
that truly showcases our characters?
It was impossible to evaluate.
Because I couldn't see the characters.
I had hardly any parts.
I was barely visible...
until the end of the first verse.
Only Hash, Simeez,
and MIN JUN had solo parts.
Then there was the group dance.
(The rest participated only in the group dance.)
The dancers didn't create a visual composition together.
There were just individuals.
There were just cool parts.
It seemed like it was merely conveying...
the choreography.
We would be...
appearing in the video during every weekly broadcast.
So I found myself wishing...
it had incorporated the dance, movement, and direction...
of various choreographers.
The dancers will look even cooler in the second verse.
Look forward to what's next.
If I get selected.
If not, you won't be able to see it.
"I'll show it in the two-minute version," he said.
He should have fit that into one minute.
I tried to fit it all into one minute,
and that's how mine turned out.
Cramming ten people?
That's not my style.
Unfortunately, that's all for the trial version.
If you want to see it, vote.
By that logic,
I wouldn't have made it that way.
I would've explained more and left it open-ended.
It's a draft video.
A movie teaser should make people...
want to watch the movie.
When looking at this teaser, it's not clear...
what direction you're taking.
They should've looked for the director's potential through...
the draft, but they only looked at the proposal itself.
This is not the director's domain.
That's the level of an ordinary person.
The choreography,
especially the chorus choreography, is good.
Because it's really catchy.
But,
the choreography isn't quite catchy enough...
to be a highlight in every episode.
It feels fresh and good when you see it for the first time.
I made it so it can be watched every time.
Koo Young and BADA already danced in perfect timing.
Honestly, I don't know why they see it as a negative.
They were already dancing.
(They're already hooked on my choreography.)
Hello, I'm choreographer-director NaiN.
(Presenting concept and draft video, next choreographer NaiN)
My concept is...
"Game of Thrones."
It's childish and simple.
But works well.
Rather than a medieval vibe,
the "Throne" concept...
is based on the game...
we're currently playing.
Rather than taking things away,
within the concept of a "game..."
we'll showcase our dance...
in the video.
It somehow feels plain.
We're not making a dance video.
It's a Title Sequence Film Mission.
It might feel a little obvious,
but since it has to be a piece that represents us,
my top priority was conveying the dance itself.
I also gave MIN JUN...
the "knees on the ground" part.
Is it the third time?
(BABYZOO's knees MIN JUN)
It won't be just slamming the knees into the ground.
I wanted the viewers...
to really see MIN JUN's knees from the ground.
See MIN JUN's knees from the ground?
(He's given up.)
I used a transparent acrylic board to convey that.
That's nice.
I felt that presenting our dance in a simple way...
would best represent who we are.
I think I took a clean approach.
NaiN would have made it really neat.
We'll show you the film.
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(Choreography Concept Credit Board: Choreographer NaiN)
I think she made it cool...
by drawing the attention in the beginning.
What is this? This is so cool.
That's good.
I really like it.
She put together the choreography really tightly.
There are many elements that make it fun.
Compositional choices and changes in camera angles.
I liked how it incorporated a variety of those.
There was more variety in the camera movement,
but nothing felt particularly new.
- That's cool. - The choreography is so cool.
The choreography was really well-made.
The choreography was well put together.
It's amazing.
The choreography of the chorus part was nice.
It made me want to dance that choreography myself.
That's so cute.
(Like this)
(That was good.)
It was really neat and trendy.
- It was nice. - It was really nice to watch.
- It feels comfortable. - It feels comfortable.
It was really neat.
After watching the clip,
the first thing that came to my mind was, "I want to try that."
When I watch something, I first check...
- if it's cool... - That's right.
And if I want to try it out.
It was a style that pretty much everyone would like.
It was a choreography that I wanted to try out.
The choreography was so cool.
The choreography of "Crown" was so cool.
If I honestly think about...
what's a cool choreography,
I think it's NaiN's performance.
You used various angles and camera movements.
You used so many elements like the location,
mirrors, and chairs.
But it was so easy to watch...
and also carried an impact.
I thought that was really smart.
I felt like they recognized what I was trying to do...
with the title sequence.
I was really happy.
- It's been a long wait. - Renan.
I was so curious to see...
what kind of concept Renan would go for.
My concept...
is "Battle Royale."
She's trying to kill us all.
(Laughing)
It tells a story about the competition...
that's taking place here.
That's so nice.
It's either the catharsis coming from the story...
or more about the choreography...
and the design.
The story is important,
but I wanted to focus as much as possible on the performance.
How will she express that?
I think I was wondering if it would work.
(Revealing Renan's choreography concept film)
That startled me.
(Hash)
Hash and I keep bending our bodies.
(The bending duo)
(BABYZOO, INGYOO, Kasper, )
(JEONG MIN JUN, Back Koo Young)
(Renan, NaiN, Simeez, Hash, BADA)
(A group twerking?)
What are they doing?
Why was there twerking all of a sudden?
That looks nice.
That's totally Renan's vibe.
Everyone's so sexy.
It's a sexy choreography.
She's pretty.
Was she focused on twerking?
I don't know why she went that far.
Why is it "Battle Royale?"
It's got red lighting.
The choreography is similar to INGYOO's.
INGYOO's chorus part is in their pre-chorus part.
Why are the dancers in such great shape?
He's tall.
Goodness.
(You can watch Renan's full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
(You can watch Simeez's full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
It was very disappointing.
The tension you mentioned from the concept...
couldn't be felt.
When I watched the video...
She should either dance to match the keyword...
or have a matching structure.
But I couldn't see that.
Maybe it's because the setting was just a practice room,
so it was hard to imagine what kind of setup we could use.
I think that's why they thought like that.
Also...
I think even if you pick five female directors,
each of them can have a very distinct character.
I don't think...
having them twerk is a good idea.
It wouldn't be right for Hash to twerk.
I can twerk if told to.
(Hash doing this?)
Twerk with my butt.
(Like this)
I can do it if told to.
But this video...
will be continuously played as the title sequence.
With that in mind...
Would it be okay to have the five women...
appear like that in the title?
I thought showing a new side...
A new challenge. That's nice, but it's not convincing.
They're not directors who rely on sexual appeal.
I don't think she made the most of the choreographer's roles.
It worked because they were foreign dancers.
She completely failed with the dancer casting.
She says it's a Title Sequence Film Mission...
It felt more like Renan's choreography video.
Finally.
I'm Director Back Koo Young.
(It's here.)
Koo Young up, Koo Young up.
I'm most curious to see his.
He's someone with experience.
I had a feeling he'd do well.
He's the person that makes me most concerned.
I'm curious to see how he'll approach it.
The title sequence film I planned...
is fast-paced,
designed to leave a subconscious impression...
of each of the ten directors.
What?
There's no concept.
Rather than something viewers simply watch and consume,
like the Leader Class Mission,
Since it's a film that introduces the start of the show,
I made the show itself the main theme.
So these are the things I've been missing.
I don't think the concept matters so much.
This film will represent...
this show and the ten directors.
But everyone really committed to the concept,
and I was confused.
My concept is to use my work...
to show who we are.
I think I'll need to really emphasize...
that all ten directors are important.
I wanted to capture all ten characters...
in just one minute.
So I thought it through.
What's that?
(That's amazing.)
I was shocked.
I thought it was really smart...
how he interpreted who these people are...
and what suits them.
I think that one minute is a failure...
if it doesn't show all of the cast's charms.
It's easy, simple,
and really stands out. I'm confident.
Let's go!
(Selecting the lowest-ranked sequence)
(Goodness)
(It was shocking.)
(Eliminate the worst performer?)
(It would be the worst feeling to get two votes.)
(From the evaluation...)
(Who will be the director that gets eliminated?)
(It's a title sequence where we appear.)
(I don't want it to be predictable.)
(I don't remember BABYZOO's.)
(That's a problem too.)
(I don't think I'll be able to shine...)
(in INGYOO's video.)
(As for the chorus part, )
(it would be a shame not to use my choreography.)
(I think I'll be able to make a much better one.)
(It's not a hooking choreography you'd want to see every episode.)
(I honestly don't know why that would be a bad thing.)
(They moved to it first.)
(I think I felt anxious.)
(I also have some trauma...)
(from self-evaluations.)
(I've never been picked...)
(in the choreographer's vote.)
(Will I end up losing again?)
(What's the worst sequence according to JEONG MIN JUN?)
(I should have said less earlier.)
(The choreographer I think...)
(I would exclude from the director candidate list is...)
(Kasper.)
(Really?)
(It was more suited for a dance video.)
(I didn't want to make...)
(a dance video I usually see.)
(That was ridiculous.)
(This is a cruel place.)
(The person I would exclude from the director candidate list...)
(I think he might pick me.)
(I thought the others would exclude MIN JUN...)
(even if I didn't.)
(The person I would exclude from the director candidate list...)
(It's really important from now on.)
(I think the key is how well I plan my strategy.)
(I could eliminate the person I'm concerned about.)
(Koo Young?)
(INGYOO?)
(Or I could eliminate someone I'm not close to.)
(What strategy will Simeez go with?)
(is BADA.)
(What? Why?)
(This makes things fun.)
(I could also eliminate people who did well.)
(Simeez chose to eliminate the person to keep in check.)
(This makes no sense.)
(I could do that.)
(That's the strategy.)
(The final director who comes out on top...)
(has the power to send someone...)
(straight to the Last Stage.)
(One of us...)
(will climb to the throne...)
(and make the rest of us work like servants.)
(Look at that.)
(What a mess.)
(I should do even better.)
(The filming location of the title sequence film of incredible scale)
(She had a very strong presence.)
(It's finally starting.)
(When it comes to impact, )
(BADA has a lot to offer.)
(She definitely has a strong presence.)
(There was a part I liked.)
(Kasper, Renan, and BABYZOO in the middle of filming)
(Your timing is too fast.)
(Even when we shot that scene, Renan's timing kept being off, )
(so we had to do several takes.)
(I think the choreography is going off-beat right now.)
(She's going off-beat?)
(Getting nervous)
(Being off beat is a serious problem for a dancer.)
(That's why we had to do so many takes.)
(Watching this, )
(I feel like I'm looking at myself in a mirror.)
(So this was why...)
(I was chosen as the worst dancer before.)
(We're talking leadership.)
(We're not evaluating students.)
(Your screen presence has so much to do...)
(with the way that you do the choreography.)
(Now, it's time...)
(to announce the final results...)
(that decides which choreographers...)
(will move on to the Last Stage.)
(I had a feeling I wouldn't make it...)
(But I think I will.)
(Glancing)
(One of them is on the right side.)
(That's so obvious, right?)
(The choreographer I think will make it to the Last Stage...)
(Renan)
(Kasper)
(Who will be the first worst choreographer...)
(to head to the Last Stage?)
(Last Stage: 24H The 3 choreographers: Renan)
(I'll hate that person forever.)